<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ROM>
  <!-- Your ROM Name -->
  <RomName>CarbonROM</RomName>
  <VersionName>R3</VersionName>
  <!-- Your ROM version. MUST be incrementally larger than previous versions -->
  <!-- Do NOT use letters in your version number. Integers only -->
  <!-- Previous version will be read from the build.prop -->
  <VersionNumber type="integer">20150910</VersionNumber>
  <!-- Linking to your files -->
    <!-- <DirectUrl><![CDATA[http://www.example.com?file=file.zip?somethingelse&anotherthing]]></DirectUrl> -->
    <!-- Use the above format if your URL has special characters in then, like an (&) ampersand -->
    <!-- Enter <DirectUrl nil="true /> or <HttpUrl nil="true /> to indicate you won't be using a type of URL -->
    <!-- HTTP link will open a web page -->
    <!-- Direct Link overrides HTTP link -->
  <DirectUrl><![CDATA[https://d8.usercdn.com/d/qql2iavzt74knvqjm3riva24lh7vxgpl3vlt5ysi5ucgtj5gpj3qegxf/CARBON-5.1.1-UNOFFICIAL-20150910-1527-armani.zip]]></DirectUrl>
  <HttpUrl><![CDATA[https://userscloud.com/tbk39u7e4k2w]]></HttpUrl>
  <!-- What version are you issuing? -->
  <Android>5.1.1</Android>
  <!-- Providing File Checking for direct downloads. You SHOULD offer this for your users whether using HTTP or Direct -->
  <!-- OPTIONAL: Enter <CheckMD5 nil="true" /> offer MD5 checking -->
  <CheckMD5 nil="true" /> 
  <!-- The filesize of your ROM -->
  <!-- Please enter this in BYTES only. Otherwise an incorrect value will be shown -->
  <FileSize type="integer">282105453</FileSize>
  <!-- Developer or Team name. You can put anything here, even a couple of names -->
  <!-- OPTIONAL: Enter <Developer nil="true" /> to hide this -->
  <Developer>Tarun93</Developer>
  <!-- Your ROM or Developer Website. Can be a personal site or your XDA/forum thread -->
  <!-- OPTIONAL: Enter <Website nil="true" /> to hide this -->
  <WebsiteURL><![CDATA[http://forum.xda-developers.com/redmi-1s/development/rom-carbon-rom-r1-beta-t3104330]]></WebsiteURL>
  <!-- Your Donate URL -->
  <!-- OPTIONAL: Enter <DonateURL nil="true" /> to hide this -->
  <!--DonateURL><![CDATA[]]></DonateURL-->
  <DonateURL nil="true" />
  <!-- Put the changelog here... Use Markdown to format it -->
  <!-- Again, surround special characters with the CDATA tags or your XML will NOT parse -->
  <Changelog>### Changelog 20150910
Project name: android_hardware_broadcom_libbt
  *Dheeraj CVR - libbt-vendor: add support for samsung bluetooth

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_bt
  *pramod kotreshappa - Bluetooth: Fix for BT crashes during preload timeout
  *pramod kotreshappa - Bluetooth: Fix for ANT standalone turn on failure
  *pramod kotreshappa - Bluetooth: Send controller logging VS cmd after wcnss filter init
  *pramod kotreshappa - Bluetooth: Fix to handle invalid VS event during patch download
  *Bhakthavatsala Raghavendra - Bluetooth: Get FW build label information from VS command
  *Scott Mertz - Bluetooth: load btaddr from NV if QCOM_BT_USE_BTNV is set
  *Srinu Jella - Bluetooth: Don't return in case external ldo is not present

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_media
  *Srinu Gorle - Revert "mm-video-v4l2: vidc: venc: Update color conversion decision"
  *Ashray Kulkarni - mm-video-v4l2: vidc: update thread names
  *Ashray Kulkarni - mm-video-v4l2: venc: fix all I frame encoding usecase
  *c_sisanj - libc2dcolorconvert: Modified stride and size calculation
  *Fred Oh - mm-core: Limit number of NT mode audio decoders
  *Ashray Kulkarni - mm-video-v4l2: venc: encoder cleanup during error handling
  *Ashray Kulkarni - mm-video-v4l2: handle flush done as buffer_done and not as cmd_done
  *Ashray Kulkarni - Revert "mm-video-v4l2: Add error handling in component_open"
  *Balamurugan Alagarsamy - mm-video-v4l2: vdec: change prefered color format default order

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_media
  *Surajit Podder - mm-video: Calculate average fps to update refresh rate
  *Ashray Kulkarni - mm-video-v4l2: handle flush done as buffer_done and not as cmd_done
  *Praveen Chavan - mm-video-v4l2: vdec: insert timestamps qeued by client in TS queue
  *Deepak Verma - mm-video: venc: Correct a typo in variable name
  *Michael Bestas - mm-video-v4l2: Remove useless build warning

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_audio
  *Thomas Wendt - hal: Tell Huawei acdb loader which files to load
  *Bruno Martins - hal: Genericize dual-SIM voice_extn implementation
  *Weiyin Jiang - post_proc: explicitly disable virtualizer module if strength is 0
  *Dhananjay Kumar - post_proc: fix crash in offload effect bundle during stop output
  *Dan Pasanen - hal: only open the amplifier once
  *Dan Pasanen - hal: enable amplifier earlier
  *ljzyal - hal: Add support for Samsung dual-SIM implementation
  *Eric Laurent - compress offload: use new sample rate representation.
  *Ethan Chen - hal: Notify amplifier of device enable/disable
  *Vidyakumar Athota - hal: update input source type during open input stream
  *Avinash Vaish - hal: Prevent de-routing in case the usecase doesn't share codec backend
  *Venkata Narendra Kumar Gutta - hal: Fix ANR if In-Call recording is started at end of voice call
  *Pavan Chikkala - hal: Update pcm_open flag for VOIP
  *Pavan Chikkala - audio: Modified atoi to atoll to convert large Numeric values
  *Ethan Chen - hal: Convert libaudioamp to audio_amplifier HAL

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_audio
  *Dhananjay Kumar - post_proc: fix crash in offload effect bundle during stop output
  *Dhananjay Kumar - post_proc: fix reverb processing issue when preset is set to NONE
  *Weiyin Jiang - post_proc: explicitly disable virtualizer module if strength is 0
  *Dan Pasanen - hal: only open the amplifier once
  *Dan Pasanen - hal: enable amplifier earlier
  *Venkata Narendra Kumar Gutta - hal: Fix voice session setup failure
  *Narsinga Rao Chella - hal: reroute active capture usecases which share same backend
  *alanht_wu - Add special case for stereo camcorder
  *Ethan Chen - hal: Notify amplifier of device enable/disable
  *Ravi Kumar Alamanda - hal: pass samplerate as is to tiny compress
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Extend platform parser to allow device name aliasing
  *Steve Kondik - msm8994: Remove bogus metadata
  *Steve Kondik - hal: Add option to use low latency as primary output
  *Rashed Abdel-Tawab - hal: Invert more build flags
  *solk2 - hal: Fix voice call recording for msm8974
  *Steve Kondik - hal: Invert standard build flags
  *Steve Kondik - hal: Fix digital USB headset combo device
  *Steve Kondik - hal: Add support for dedicated VoIP devices
  *Bhalchandra Gajare - hal: Fix sidetone sequence during voice call
  *Steve Kondik - hal: Clean up compilation warnings
  *Ethan Chen - hal: Convert libaudioamp to audio_amplifier HAL
  *Scott Mertz - audio: add amplifier stream start/standby operations
  *Daniel Hillenbrand - hal: Support the audio amplifier hook
  *Ravi Kumar Alamanda - hal: pass samplerate as is to tiny compress

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_audio
  *Thomas Wendt - hal: Tell Huawei acdb loader which files to load
  *Eric Laurent - compress offload: use new sample rate representation.
  *Venkata Narendra Kumar Gutta - hal: Fix voice session setup failure
  *Zhou Song - hal: allow to get render position for non-offload use cases
  *Ravi Kumar Alamanda - hal: ensure EC reference is disabled before enabling
  *Zhou Song - audio_hal: increase written frames size when HAL is in SSR
  *Weiyin Jiang - post_proc: remove unnecessary command size check
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Only allow non-legacy HAL
  *Ethan Chen - hal: Correctly set backend to best available parameters

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_audio
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Notify amplifier of device enable/disable
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Refactor amplifier_set_device logic
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Convert libaudioamp to audio_amplifier HAL
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Make audio device accessible to HAL functions

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_keymaster
  *Scott Mertz - keymaster: fix build for msm8994
  *Rashed Abdel-Tawab - keystore: Enable building on msm8992 and msm8994

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_display
  *Naseer Ahmed - hwc: Handle DOZE_SUSPEND properly
  *Baldev Sahu - hwc: Ensure pipe unset is called before wfd commit
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "hwc: Skip load based composition for video playback."

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_display
  *Naseer Ahmed - hwc: Handle DOZE_SUSPEND properly
  *Baldev Sahu - hwc: Ensure pipe unset is called before wfd commit
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "hwc: Skip load based composition for video playback."

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_display
  *Rama Vaddula - Revert "libmemtrack: Properly account for memory usage"
  *Saurabh Shah - hwc/hdmi: Return FB attributes to f/w for active config
  *Ranjith Kagathi Ananda - gralloc: Fix RAW10 stride
  *Saurabh Shah - hwc: Limit BWC to content with height within 4092
  *Arun Kumar K.R - hwc: Handle layers marked as PROTECTED flag as secure
  *Scott Mertz - Revert "hqd: Use MSM_VIDC_TARGET_LIST for Venus color format"
  *Arun Kumar K.R - hwc: Fix incorrect compType for HWCursor
  *Arun Kumar K.R - display: Add support for HW Cursor
  *Saurabh Shah - hwc: Reset mode tracking in MDPComp constructor

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_display
  *Saurabh Shah - hwc: Reserve pipes for video layers first
  *radhakrishna - hwc: Avoid MDP comp for RGB downscaled layer
  *radhakrishna - hwc: Handle multiple YUV layer use case in low end targets
  *Raj Kamal - hwc: Avoid updating refresh-rate if already done
  *Saurabh Shah - hwc: Use GPU to compose for smaller updates
  *Raj Kamal - hwc: Set refresh rate during idlefallback for unhandled cases
  *Raj Kamal - hwc: Donot rely on previous comp type to trigger idlefallback
  *Raj Kamal - hwc: Roundoff the input fps to nearest standard fps
  *Raj Kamal - hwc: Trigger dynamic refresh-rate change for more usecases
  *Praveena Pachipulusu - hwc: Reset the refresh rate alone to avoid stack corruption.
  *Shimrit Malichi - liblight: Add support for bluetooth LED

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_display
  *Saurabh Shah - hwc: Bump up version to 1.4

Project name: android_hardware_qcom_fm
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - FMRadio : Keep track of scanned frequencies in service
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - FMRadio : Ensure scan state is kept in sync
  *AdrianDC - QComFM : Allow the FM Transmitter to be reactivated
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - FMRecord: Grant REAL_GET_TASKS
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *lijun.xie - FM: The collect channel disappear when quit FM
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Martin Brabham - Fix status text to reflect when FM is enabled.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Hamster Tian - FM: fix mRadioTextScroller usage in transmitter activity
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_hardware_ti_wpan
  *Michael Gernoth - libbt-vendor-ti: add ssr_cleanup

Project name: android_hardware_ti_wlan
  *Michael Bestas - wl12xx: Fix compilation warnings
  *Dmitry Shmidt - ti: Add interface_mtu request

Project name: android_hardware_ti_omap4
  *Ziyan - camera: add support for espresso

Project name: android_hardware_libhardware
  *Steve Kondik - libhardware: Add POWER_HINT_LAUNCH_BOOST for PowerHAL
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Notify amplifier HAL of device enable/disable
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Add getNumEnrollmentSteps [2/2]
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint [2/2]: Numerous Fingerprint Improvements
  *Scott Mertz - Fingerprint: add explicit authenticate actions
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Add audio amplifier HAL

Project name: x86_64-linux-android-4.9
  *Dan Albert - Update gold to build #2098274.

Project name: arm-eabi-4.9
  *Chet Kener - 9-1-2015 - 4.9.4 UBERTC Snapshot

Project name: arm-linux-androideabi-4.9
  *Chet Kener - 9-1-2015 - 4.9.4 UBERTC Snapshot

Project name: android_prebuilts_cmsdk
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update api level 2 for PersistentStorage.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update latest api text file.
  *Yvonne Wong - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update api text for CMSettings
  *Yvonne Wong - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update api text for Hardware
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Always do release deploy for current.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update development platform sdk jar.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update for CMTelephonyManager.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Provide maven deployment modules.
  *Matt Garnes - Add SettingsManager and CyanogenModAlarmClock APIs to API level 2.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update api text for ProfileTrigger.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Publish new version of future-release cmsdk.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: @hide PARCELEABLE_VERSION.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update api level 1 for hotfix.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update bleeding edge sdk for recent changes.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update latest api text for recent changes.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Rewrite current cmsdk version (API level 1) for hotfix.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update for future* cmsdk changes.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Make sure readme is markdown format.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Fix spelling error.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update for API level naming.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Create and update 2nd api level text files.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update perms file for API level 2.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update readme for perms.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update readme.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Create new future-release blobs.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Update API text for API level 1.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Add prebuilt jars for cmsdk.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Add api text files for API level 1.
  *Adnan Begovic - prebuilts/cmsdk: Add declared permission info for API level 1.
  *Abhisek Devkota - Initial empty repository

Project name: git-repo
  *Dan Willemsen - Revert "GITC: Always update the gitc manifest from the repo manifest"
  *Dan Willemsen - GITC: Always update the gitc manifest from the repo manifest
  *Dan Willemsen - _CopyAndLinkFiles even if the sources haven't changed
  *Simran Basi - GITC: Fix repo sync.
  *Dan Willemsen - gitc: Improve help visibility
  *Dan Willemsen - Fix gitc check if gitc isn't installed
  *Simran Basi - GITC: Pull GITC Manifest Dir from the config.
  *Simran Basi - GITC: Expand relative remote URLs.
  *Simran Basi - GITC: Add repo start support.
  *David Pursehouse - project.py: Improve message shown when hook is not replaced
  *David Pursehouse - project.py: Consistently use the _error method to print error messages
  *Dan Willemsen - Smartsync: Don't fail if there isn't a cookiefile
  *David Pursehouse - Sync: Refactor netrc parsing
  *David Pursehouse - gitc_init: Remove unused import
  *David Pursehouse - gitc_utils: Fix incorrect string format argument
  *David Pursehouse - gitc_utils: Remove unused variable
  *David Pursehouse - gitc_utils: Remove unused import; add missing import
  *Dan Willemsen - Support smart-sync through persistent-http[s]
  *David Pursehouse - Fix formatting of message when retrying clone
  *Simran Basi - GITC: Add repo sync support.
  *Dan Willemsen - Copy clone-depth in `repo manifest`
  *Simran Basi - GITC: Add gitc-init subcommand to repo.
  *Simon Ruggier - Include project path in --force-sync error message
  *Dan Willemsen - Fix shallow clone behavior
  *Simon Ruggier - Include dest-branch attribute in the 'manifest' subcommand's output
  *Dan Sandler - Emit project info in case of sync exception.
  *Dan Willemsen - Fix _ReferenceGitDir symlinking
  *Graham Christensen - Support filtering by group on forall and list subcmd
  *Kevin Degi - Add option to correct gitdir when syncing
  *Cassidy Burden - Prevent repo info from crashing when default element doesn't exist.
  *Kevin Degi - InitGitDir: Clean up created directories
  *David Pursehouse - Revert "Add --prune option to fetch when syncing a mirror repo"
  *Kevin Degi - project.RemoteFetch: Handle depth cases more robustly
  *Conley Owens - Always output upstream if specified
  *David Pursehouse - forall: use smart sync override manifest if it exists
  *David Pursehouse - sync: Remove smart sync override manifest when not in smart sync mode
  *David Pursehouse - forall: Don't try to get lrev of projects in mirror workspace
  *David Pursehouse - sync: Improve error message when writing smart sync manifest fails
  *Than McIntosh - Fix 'repo cherry-pick' to avoid hanging on commit-msg update.
  *Jarkko Pöyry - Improve error message when syncing a project with invalid groups.
  *Anthony King - forall: setenv, only encode val if encode exists
  *Anthony King - init: don't call urllib.parse
  *Anthony King - git_config: fix _SaveJson typo
  *Anthony King - error: fix typos
  *Anthony King - git_command: only decode when needed
  *Anthony King - decode the buffer before appending
  *Wink Saville - Teach _LinkFile._Link to handle globs.
  *Colin Cross - Make linkfile symlinks relative

Project name: android
  *Ethan Chen - manifest: Remove separate paths for 8610/8226 HALs
  *Myself5 - manifest: add CarbonWallpapers
  *weldoncyngn - adding android-support-test for espresso test
  *Arnav Gupta - manifest: move mips prebuilts into notdefault
  *Myself5 - You are not a CM repo
  *Myself5 - manifest: rewrite to be able to pick from CM gerrit
  *Abhisek Devkota - Fixup Freetype project & revision
  *Myself5 - update readme for lp5.1
  *Joey Hewitt - CVE Fix, track higher rev of conscrypt
  *PhaseBurn - Adding qcom sepolicy globally
  *Ryan N. Norris - Fix cmsdk repo path.
  *Patrick Campanale - Added our fork of cmsdk
  *Brint E. Kriebel - manifest: Update to freetype 2.6.0
  *Myself5 - Revert "Changed a few repos"
  *Patrick Campanale - Changed a few repos that we are resetting a few weeks back to fix some bugs
  *Myself5 - Fix Derp
  *Brandon McAnsh - cm: Use fork of aarch64 gcc for darwin as well
  *Steve Kondik - cm: Use fork of aarch64 gcc
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - 5.1.1_r3 -> 5.1.1_r6
  *José Adolfo Galdámez - manifest: remove final > extra
  *Adnan Begovic - Add cmsdk prebuilts repo.
  *Abhisek Devkota - Add Android Support Library prebuilts
  *STELIX - Manifest - Fix another stupid derp
  *Steve Kondik - Manifest - Switch to cm fork of external/lzma
  *Sean Hoyt - Remove device specfic exynos repo
  *STELIX - Manifest - Fix a stupid derp
  *STELIX - Manifest - track our own...
  *Myself5 - manifest: change the way to handle our repos
  *Michael Bestas - Manifest - Remove external/srec
  *STELIX - Manifest - use some our own telephony stuff

Project name: android_vendor_xiaomi
  *fefifofum - Use prebuilt libOmxVdecHevc
  *tarun93 - skip mpdecision n thermal blobs

Project name: cm_platform_sdk
  *Matt Garnes - Allow whitelist for MODIFY_NETWORK_SETTINGS permission.
  *Matt Garnes - Add Hotword audio capture constants.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update documentation for Boysenberry release.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update documentation for HAF permission.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update tests for new ALARM permissions.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update cm-api for hasSensitiveData() and new permissions.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add permissions for ALARMS.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Enforce cyanogenmod.permission.MODIFY_PROFILES for profiles.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Fix toast in CMHardwareTest.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add preliminary hardware manager tests.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Change parceling for DisplayMode.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Fix spelling error in CMSettingsProvider makefile.
  *BadDaemon - BugFix: Fix potential NPEs with getService()
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmsdk: allow custom tiles to set the new qstile's sensitive data flag
  *Yvonne Wong - Add CMSettingsProvider and CMDatabaseHelper
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Build in the Manifest and R classes for the sdk.
  *Yvonne Wong - cmsdk: Update cm api text files
  *Steve Kondik - cmhw: Add makeDefault arg to setDisplayMode
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Steve Kondik - cmsdk: Add initial DisplayMode and AutoContrast support to CMHW
  *Steve Kondik - cmsdk: Transplant CMHW into CMSDK
  *Steve Kondik - profiles: Don't bind the keyguard until ActivityManager is up
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Rename gradle-sample package namespace.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add gradle sample project.
  *Jon Dinneen - cmsdk: Fix README. (Add period).
  *Roman Birg - cmsdk: fix enabling/disabling keyguard
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update readme for maven central deploy.
  *Patrick Campanale - Changed to Carbon vendor
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update README
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Provide quick manual functional telephony api tests.
  *Joao Figueiredo - cmsdk: Dual SIM support on CM SDK
  *Matt Garnes - Update APIs for new settings and DeskClock support.
  *Matt Garnes - Add API to SettingsManager to set zen mode.
  *Matt Garnes - Add AlarmClock support for CM DeskClock manipulation.
  *Matt Garnes - Add SettingsManager.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add sample Profiles application.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Expose ProfileTrigger constructor for third parties.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update custom tile sample for shouldCollapsePanel.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Clean up documentation.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update current api text files.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Support deleteIntent and remove tiles when packages change.
  *Roman Birg - Profiles: add LockModeSettings
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add support for remote views in expanded styles
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add functional manual and unit tests for new setIcon
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Create new setIcon method for utilizing bitmaps
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Make sure we're writing ProfileTrigger values as typed array.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Fix Profile parceling for custom objects.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update tests for recent builder changes.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Make sure we're defauling shouldCollapsePanel to true.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update manual functional tests for shouldCollapsePanel.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add unit tests for shouldCollapsePanel
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add method for shouldCollapsePanel.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Hide PARCELABLE_VERSION constant which varies between releases.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update api text for recent changes.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add tests for StatusBarPanelCustomTile parceling.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Declare a parcelable header.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Make sure we're not including source from internal package.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update intent action extras to match new namespace.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Fix javadoc comment for CM_VERSION_CODES.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update api files for intent action change.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update PROFILE_PICKER intent action.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Clean up constant linking for javadoc.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Return UNKNOWN for impossible sdk ints.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add documentation for validating API level.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add copyright header for ProfileManagerTest.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add functional manual test for custom uri publish tile.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add unit tests for CustomTile parceling.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add simple profile manager tests.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add unit tests for Profile parceling.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add unit tests for versioning with os.Build
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Fix Profile parceling.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add CMStatusBarManager and CustomTile.Builder tests.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update profiles functional tests.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Clear calling identity when resetAll is called.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Add boysenberry to api text.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Name api level 2 as boysenberry.
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmsdk: fix cannot create handler
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update api text files.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Target 2nd API level on documentation generation.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: @hide everything relating to ProfileGroups, until complete.
  *Adnan Begovic - cmsdk: Update profile settings documentation.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Begin documentation and testing for profiles.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Utilize CMSDK_PACKAGE_ID.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Introduce factored out resources from framework.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Make sure to initialize ProfileTriggerHelper.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Introduce Profiles API from frameworks.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Update iconography for resource package.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Only target specific packages for checkapi.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Add SINCE API level for docs.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmsdk: notify new listeners all registered custom tiles
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmsdk: customtiles: allow load resources from external packages
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmsdk: fix customtile listener service registering logic
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmsdk: do not crash system if CustomTileListenerService isn't present
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Update current and system api texts.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Utilize a SparseArray instead of Map, avoid autoboxing.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Update for versioning tests.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Create versioning for platform SDK.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Update tests for ExpandedStyles
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Document the capabilities of ExpandedStyles for CustomTile.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Update samples for expanded styles.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Create support for ExpandedStyles in CustomTiles.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Actually hide ThemeVersion.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Add check-api generated texts.
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Setup initial check-api mechanism.
  *Andy Mast - Introduce Theme Versioning [2/2]
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - CMSDK: Hide CMContextConstants from docs.

Project name: android_vendor_carbon
  *Myself5 - vendor: compile CarbonWallpapers
  *Kra1o5 - Update Spain APNs
  *Abhisek Devkota - Update India APNs to YU list
  *Luca Stefani - vendor/cm: add curl to build
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Start building in CMSettingsProvider.
  *Abhisek Devkota - Fix Airtel APN Selection
  *Davis Mosenkovs - Updated APN settings for Latvian operators
  *Abhisek Devkota - Rogers LTE apn fix?
  *Marcos Marado - Fix Movistar APNs.
  *Steve Kondik - cm: Moving CMHW to CMSDK
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Don't be so noisy.
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Expose internal revision for platform.
  *Kra1o5 - Add new Tuenti MNC SPN override name
  *Arvin Quilao - APN: Update configurations for Philippine networks
  *PhaseBurn - Adding cert, renaming builds...
  *Myself5 - replace wrong vendor path
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Always use gpg sign-and-deploy for deployments.
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Provide means of uploading an artifact to maven.
  *Joao Figueiredo - cmsdk: Dual SIM support on CM SDK
  *Matt Garnes - Add SettingsManagerService from cmsdk as a system service.
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - apns: zero-length items are evil and break auto-selection
  *Marcos Marado - Clean up MEO/TMN APNs
  *Abhisek Devkota - Remove 'preferred' no-op
  *dianlujitao - Update APN for China Telecom
  *zh0122 - Add a bash completion "--force-sync" for repo sync
  *ginnungagap - Update #comment to reflect removal of /data/local/userinit.d/ support
  *Chris Sarbora - Specify the maven-dependency-plugin version directly so as to force Maven 3.0.5 to use the correct version.
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Clean up paths to known files.
  *Patrick - Fix Rogers APN
  *Abhisek Devkota - APN fine tuning
  *Chris Sarbora - Hack in support for the old version of Maven that Ubuntu apparently ships with
  *Lin Ma - rendang: Remove unwanted APNs
  *Abhisek Devkota - CYNGNOS-454 - Fix config_preferred_apn Overrides
  *Brandon McAnsh - sepolicy: system_app: Remove performace setting related entries
  *Abhisek Devkota - Yet another massive APN list
  *Steve Kondik - cm: Update properties and libs for stagefright-plugins
  *Zyg0te - Updated APN for Austrian Carrier Yesss.
  *Chris Sarbora - Prevent Maven target from grabbing transitive dependencies
  *Abhisek Devkota - Additional APN cleanup and modifications
  *NBruderman - Vendor: Fix "mts" carrier password
  *Abhisek Devkota - Additional European MVNOs
  *Abhisek Devkota - Massive APN Update
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: overlay start for ProfileService in external framework.
  *Michael Bestas - Remove obsolete /cache/dalvik-cache stuff from init.local.rc
  *Jake Jackson - Fix Sprint 3G
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Represent as CyanogenMod API's
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Remove search widget from developer docs.
  *Adnan Begovic - vendor/cm: Point to proper prebuilts/cmsdk directories.
  *Chris Sarbora - Support downloading from Maven
  *Steve Kondik - cm: Update stagefright-plugins depdendencies
  *Ethan Chen - Revert "cm: Add import for prebundled APKs"
  *Steve Kondik - cm: Add backup API key for Trebuchet
  *Konsta - Update Sonera APNs
  *Chenxi Mao - apn: Add China Telecomm 4G APN support
  *Adnan Begovic - cm: Point to the right files for checkapi-cm.
  *Adnan Begovic - CM: Provide apicheck and cm-specific config inheritance.
  *Dan Pasanen - init: stop ril daemons if ro.radio.noril is set
  *Matt Mower - Update Ting GSM APNs
  *c457 - add MetroPCS's IPv6 APN
  *Abhisek Devkota - Deprecate epc.tmobile.com APN
  *Phil Eichinger - APNs: Correct MMSC for HoT Austria
  *Zyg0te - apns: Removed APN configuration for Noverca.
  *Brandon McAnsh - config: Create TV targets (full and mini)
  *Evan Widger - Temp fix for Bouygues telecom issues
  *Lin Ma - FOTA: Create /cache/recovery in init.rc for FOTA
  *Christian Oder - invite i9100 to the party
  *Patrick Campanale - Add w7
  *Patrick Campanale - Working on shamu
  *Adnan Begovic - CM: Make sure we're parsing api versions for cmsdk docs.
  *Matt Mower - Fix invalid roaming_protocol for telenor.smart APN
  *Abhisek Devkota - Drop hipri,supl from Smartfren4G

Project name: testing
  *Juan Pereira - Add view matcher for input type on an edittext
  *Juan Pereira - Add view matcher for matching error text on an edittext
  *Jake Wharton - Add drawer layout open/close action factories.
  *Damián Arrillaga - Add IntentTestRule three parameters constructor to be fully compatible with ActivityTestRule.
  *Damián Arrillaga - Fix RecyclerViewActions actionOnItem doc
  *Eric Denman - Specify gravity on the "is the drawer open/closed" checks

Project name: android_frameworks_base
  *Myself5 - Convert Slim Float drawables to vectors and add Dark Version
  *Myself5 - [2/2] Base: Add Button to Recents to open App as Floating
  *rogersb11 - Slim action float tile Graphics
  *BlackDragon - Floating windows: Fix statusbar immersive mode for snap points.
  *rogersb11 - Gesture anywhere floating switch 1/2
  *sd3993 - Do not launch floating window when on default launcher
  *lion0738 - [1/2] Base: option to launch heads up in floating mode.
  *BlackDragon - Floating windows: Fix minimize/maximize buttons coloring.
  *BlackDragon - Floating windows: Fix when we close floating window also remove the task.
  *rogersb11 - Notifications: Launch in floating mode button.
  *BlackDragon - Floating windows update: Fixes and Improvements.
  *BlackDragon - Recents: Launch as Floating app.
  *BlackDragon - Remove: "Recents: Launch as floating app."
  *LorDClockaN - Chrome floating fix:
  *Evan Anderson - Dismiss IME when floating window is dismissed
  *oreiche - Keep app when opening floating window from recents panel
  *BigBrother1984 - Forward Port: Floating Window with Multitasking.
  *Myself5 - Revert "FW_Base - instant reboot action trigger (1/2)"
  *Rabih Salamey - base: gut out soft reboot
  *LorDClockaN - FWB: Toast icon switch (1/2)
  *Steve Kondik - power: Boost improvements
  *Daniel Martí - Add basic support for VorbisComment DATE tags
  *Diogo Ferreira - SystemUI: Fix blinking when reported battery level is 0
  *Jorge Ruesga - systemui: left hand navigation ring
  *Jorge Ruesga - systemui: respect navigation rings configuration
  *d34d - Ringtones: Allow excluding from removable storage
  *Matt Garnes - Allow CAPTURE_AUDIO_HOTWORD to be whitelisted by signature.
  *Steve Kondik - power: Add a new power hint for application launches
  *Mikalacki Sava - SystemUI: fix NPE crash when Visualizer is not initialized
  *Jorge Ruesga - systemui: wait for animation end before take a screenshoot
  *d34d - Spam: Close writable DB after use
  *Mykola Kondratenko - zygote: fix memory leak when fork process
  *d34d - Fingerprint: don't start auth if not showing
  *Roman Birg - Allow default system profile state to be overlayed
  *d34d - Keyguard: Remove bouncer when re-registering status bar
  *d34d - Show infinity for large notification counts
  *Gabriele M - Let liblights adjust the brightness of LEDs while previewing it
  *d34d - Notifications: Only check for spam if new
  *Abhisek Devkota - Remove duplicate audio: Tejat is Argon
  *d34d - Fingerprint: Allow disabling of vibration
  *Danesh M - SystemUI : Toggle nav item visibility based on IME
  *Adnan Begovic - PackageManager: Move fingerprint feature out of android namespace.
  *Michael Bestas - core/SystemUI: Remove zh-rHK CAF translations
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - SystemUI: check RecentsConfiguration isn't null before running RecentsTaskLoader
  *Hamster Tian - ResolverActivity: reduce elevation to make it flat
  *Jorge Ruesga - base: hide qs tiles with sensitive data
  *Myself5 - base: Fixup "SystemUI: use new visualizer from Eleven" for MSIM Devices
  *Roman Birg - SettingsProvider: don't set default value for advanced mode
  *ghepeu - Add support for Samsung extended AGPS
  *stofstik - Added show volume panel tile to QS
  *AdrianDC - LEDs Brightness [2/2]: Lights notifications brightness support
  *AdrianDC - Lights with Screen On [1/2]: Optional allowment of lights
  *Raj Yengisetty - SystemUI: do not load header bar if boot isn't complete
  *d34d - Set mProximity to PROXIMITY_UNKNOWN on screen off
  *Roman Birg - Fingerprint Service: fix potential NPE
  *HazouPH - [1/2] Camera button support
  *d34d - Show icon of package associated with Toast
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - Fix "Select correct 12 or 24 time format" breaking Chrome
  *d34d - Themes: Use warning level logging for getBootTheme
  *d34d - NavRing: Update search assistant drawable
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - Select correct 12 or 24 time format according to Locale
  *d34d - Themes: Compose icons that just have scale defined
  *maxwen - SystemUI: time-context header fixes
  *xplodwild - [1/2] SystemUI: Add time-context headers to the notification header
  *Myself5 - This one was not supposed to be in there.
  *lion0738 - SystemUI: Fade keyguard visualizer along with other icons
  *Scott Mertz - androidfw: fix cmsdk attribute lookup
  *Chirayu Desai - Add the user set network mode to the siminfo table
  *Scott Mertz - add config for proximity check on screen on default value
  *Utkarsh Gupta - SystemUI: use new visualizer from Eleven
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *blong - Filter internal account when set device owner
  *Vinay Verma - Modify SILENT profile to restrict notification sound
  *Sashidhar Ganiga - Fix return to task when single task activity is brought to front
  *jinchul.kim - Trim task thumbnail within MAX_RECENT_BITMAPS.
  *Nitin Shivpure - Bluetooth: Check for mPanservice before changing tethering state
  *Kiran Kelageri - Bluetooth: Fix for crash in multi advertiser
  *Jack Yoo - Keyguard: Adding null check for dateformat
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Themes: Allow packages to be set as non-themeable
  *d34d - Fingerprint: Don't start fingerprint auth in constructor
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - DevicePolicy: Restore backup manager if the device owner is cleared
  *myfluxi - backup: Fix the system server crash fix
  *Steve Kondik - livedisplay: Fix boot-time race condition
  *Steve Kondik - cmhw: Move CMHW out of the framework and into CMSDK
  *Steve Kondik - cmsdk: Start external services at the right time
  *d34d - Fingerprint: Call SecurityCallback.dismiss when recognized
  *Amit Mahajan - DO NOT MERGE Change to add STK_PERMISSION for stk related commands.
  *Wale Ogunwale - Prevent system uid component from running in an app process
  *Michael Bestas - Fix wrong Hungarian translation
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Revert "Revert "Wait until the Keyguard is drawn to dismiss the boot dialog.""
  *Brandon McAnsh - Revamp 'Stay awake' choices
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - SignalStrength: Allow for custom signal buckets in LTE
  *Jorge Ruesga - base: don't refresh visualizer tile once the tile is destroyed
  *Roman Birg - Revert "Barrier only messages shouldn't prevent the idle handlers from running"
  *Roman Birg - Themes: don't recreateDefaults on typeface when locale changes
  *Veeti Paananen - Disable PIN entry after successful quick unlock
  *Marcel Dopita - Fix forcing media stream control on tablet
  *Adnan Begovic - systemui: Provide empty view for empty lists published in QSTile.
  *Apoorv Raghuvanshi - audio: Playback over USB DAC connected before boot
  *louis_chang - [ActivityManager] Bring up Service if not schedule to restart
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - PBD: Apply the same emmc discard logic as ext4_utils
  *d34d - Keyguard: Don't show keyguard if CryptKeeper enabled
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: add missed super window calls
  *Wale Ogunwale - Lockdown AM.getRunningAppProcesses API with permission.REAL_GET_TASKS
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *emancebo - Fix telephony property access for CDMA rewrite rules in PhoneNumberUtils
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Kra1o5 - National roaming info for new Tuenti MNC in Spain
  *Matt Garnes - Fix intent resolution of default preferred apps.
  *Roman Birg - PhoneWinowManager: resolve home car intent
  *Altaf-Mahdi - Themes: Theme power off and reboot dialog
  *d34d - Keyguard: Stop fingerprint auth when not showing
  *Qiang Chen - Fix StrictMode violation during getDefaultApn()
  *Kun Liang - AppOps: fix delete ops wrongly matched issue
  *Sashidhar Ganiga - frameworks/base: synchronize surface control object access.
  *spooja - frameworks/base: Fix ContentService JNI leaks
  *d34d - Fix memory leak in AAPT
  *d34d - Make MANAGE_DOCUMENTS permission signature|system
  *Roman Birg - LockPatternUtils: add a static way to retreive pattern from string
  *dankoman - [1/3] Frameworks: Proximity speaker
  *Myself5 - Fix double added case definition
  *Myself5 - Fix missed Derp with missing /**
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - Keyguard: Don't disable visibility when scrambling pin.
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: update to use new Profiles LockSettings obj
  *Adnan Begovic - systemui: Support remote expanded style.
  *Adnan Begovic - SystemUI: Add support for external bitmap icons.
  *Danesh M - CaptivePortal : Ensure uri is not null
  *kai.cao - autobrightness: Fix the brightness dialog is not work when first enable auto-backlight
  *Abhisek Devkota - Duplicate Alarm: Fermium == Argon
  *Abhisek Devkota - Remove duplicate alarm
  *d34d - CustomQSTile: Check for bad identifier in getTitle()
  *Roman Birg - PackageManager: copy allowViaWhitelist flag for perm trees
  *Steve Kondik - systemui: Fix various issues with transparent bars
  *Steve Kondik - wm: Underp WindowManager flags
  *Steve Kondik - camera: Unbreak the extended face detection code
  *Pat Erley - ActivityManagerService: Don't export 'system' process in running app list
  *Jorge Ruesga - qs: initialize day temperature in livedisplay tile
  *Adnan Begovic - SystemUi: Respect shouldCollapsePanel when handling onClick.
  *Roman Birg - framework: add config_ledCanPulse overlay setting
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - pm: remove stale permissions
  *Mohammed Irfan - SystemUI: Crash fix from bad camera values.
  *Jorge Ruesga - base: check nullability of ConnectivityManager#getNetworkCapabilities()
  *d34d - Only clear icon cache when theme/icon pack applied
  *Mohammed Irfan - Guard in short-circuit evaluations for stringSplit methods.
  *Andy Mast - CYNGNOS-489: Fingerprint: Fix concurrent mod exception when getting Fingerprint list
  *laufersteppenwolf - Fix GPS for old GPS HALs
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *nadlabak - PhoneNumberUtils: Add rewrite rule for CDMA networks in Ukraine
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: update notification clipping when reset
  *Adnan Begovic - SettingsProvider: Update action for Profile picker.
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Add break after MSG_REMOVED
  *Andy Mast - Authenticate When Keyguard Resumes From Camera
  *Abhisek Devkota - Lazy Fix: "More Settings" localization
  *Steve Kondik - livedisplay: Round values up
  *d34d - Track current user id in ThemeService
  *Michael Bestas - Fix mounting of non-FAT formatted SD cards (1/2)
  *Danesh M - MediaScanner: Add support for default ringtones per sim
  *Chirayu Desai - Revert CAF's default system sound settings
  *STELIX - Fw_Base - Slim Heads-Up Basestatusbar missing part
  *Daniel Koman - SystemUI: fix heads up snooze button
  *Daniel Koman - SystemUI: better choice for heads up snooze icon
  *Jean-Pierre Rasquin - [2/2] SlimHeadsUp: Add a global 3-way switch
  *STELIX - Fw_Base - StatBarExpHeader: remove heads-up button from layout
  *STELIX - Fw_Base - SystemUI QS: add RebootTile manifest permissions
  *STELIX - Revert "SystemUI: add HeadsUp button in status bar header (1/2)"
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: Be sure heads up view is attached before removing it
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: Only set package name on user heads ups
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: Slim heads up customizations for LP (1/2)
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - HeadsUp options [1/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - HeadsUp: add timeout option (1/2)"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - HeadsUp: check if headsup is attached and not null when adding view"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - [Heads up swipe] Disable by default"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - [Heads up] Add touch outside event"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - [Heads up] Touch outside to hide (1/2)"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - HeadsUp: fix headsup for incoming calls"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_base - [Heads up] Don't show heads up while IME is showing"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - HeadsUp: Don't reset Y coordinate and improve edge swipe readability"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Fix heads up dismiss not working"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - QS: Add Headsup tile [1/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - QS: Add drawables for HeadsUp tile."
  *STELIX - Revert "Fix Heads-up tile transparency in off state"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Add Feature: Heads Up custom text/background color/transparency"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Improve HeadsUp [1/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Changes in Heads up qs tile"
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Update to Heads Up"
  *STELIX - Revert "Base: HeadsUp snooze function [1/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "Fix low battery exception with custom Heads Up colors"
  *STELIX - Revert "Fix heads up default colors"
  *STELIX - Revert "Heads Up: no custom text color in power save mode"
  *Steve Kondik - livedisplay: Fix issue where settings weren't applied
  *Brandon McAnsh - CaptivePortal: Remove captive_portal_login intent-filter
  *Brandon McAnsh - CaptivePortal: Assert dataUri to prevent possible NPE
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Revert "Bluetooth: Check for mPanservice before changing tethering state"
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard Fingerprint: Send Unlock Stats
  *Roman Birg - SettingsProvider: add overlay for SWAP_VOLUME_KEYS_ON_ROTATION
  *Howard M. Harte - Fix build break introduced in 83b589ec9c743174ac473622adb3f759e9d598af
  *ed.mancebo - Update indonesia country code in PhoneNumberUtils
  *emancebo - When calling indonesia using +62 prefix while already in indonesia, replace +62 prefix with 0 (CDMA only)
  *Adnan Begovic - core: Continue stripping out Profiles related code.
  *d34d - Account for cmsdk resources when attaching theme assets
  *Adnan Begovic - androidfw: Declare and load cmsdk resource package w/ id.
  *Adnan Begovic - core: Factor out profiles related resources.
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Add getNumEnrollmentSteps [1/2]
  *Jorge Ruesga - qs: fix NPE in visualizer tile
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard Fingerprint: Lock immediately when fp is used [1/2]
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: more keyguard visualizer tweaks
  *LuK1337 - msim: Fix saving default sim from select SIM dialog (1/2)
  *Roman Birg - WallpaperManagerService: use a single file observer
  *Matt Garnes - Fingerprint: Vibrate device.
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: fix keyguard unlock drawable not updating
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Get current user id via Process.myUserHandle()
  *d34d - Add fingerprint to DB before calling clients
  *Roman Birg - Fix keyguard wallpaper issues
  *Roman Birg - improve lock screen wallpaper behavior
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard Fingerprint: Don't cancel if device doesn't have the feature
  *Andy Mast - SystemUI: Add uses-permission for fingerprint
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Secure the dump
  *Henrik Baard - Remove memory leak in PersistentDataBlockService jni
  *Lucas Gomez Jimenez - DO NOT MERGE Fix JNI global references leak in AudioEffect
  *jshe32X - Avoid AsyncTask ThreadPool leak in RecentTaskLoaser
  *Steve Kondik - backup: Fix a system server crash
  *Abhisek Devkota - Even more duplicates
  *Utkarsh Gupta - Rewrite Keyguard Visualizer
  *Andy Mast - Add fingerprint permission [1/2]
  *Steve Kondik - Add a few more default QS tiles
  *Steve Kondik - livedisplay: Fix outdoor mode detection
  *Christian Poetzsch - Barrier only messages shouldn't prevent the idle handlers from running
  *Emmanuel Berthier - Add Process IOWAIT info to ANR dump
  *Snild Dolkow - Avoid ANR loop because of queued-up ANR runnables
  *Charles Tsai - Use isolated thread to perform onStart()
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: dismiss brightness slider on screen off
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Reset state when client cancels
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard: Increase time to show hint texts
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard: Add fingerprint icon to the bottom view
  *LuK1337 - SystemUI: Fix FC when mHandler is null
  *Svet Ganov - DO NOT MERGE Don't take flags when creating app widget config activity.
  *Deepanshu Gupta - Remove implementation of deprecated method.
  *Leon Scroggins III - Make Bitmap_createFromParcel check the color count. DO NOT MERGE
  *Diego Perez - Do not paint shadow if outside of the clip area
  *Deepanshu Gupta - Add Asset management support for fonts.
  *Christopher Tate - Mark persistent apps as such when the ProcessRecord is created
  *Rob - Revert "Wait until the Keyguard is drawn to dismiss the boot dialog."
  *d34d - Store manifest hash code in PackageParser.Package
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard: Show retry text on unidentified fingerprint
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: fix clock jumping when expanding QS from lockscreen
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard: Show fallback after 2 failed auth attempts
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard: Authenticate with fingerprint
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Scott Mertz - Fingerprint: disallow API calls when fingerprint is not available
  *Matt Garnes - Wait until the Keyguard is drawn to dismiss the boot dialog.
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - WhisperPush: allowing whitelisting of needed framework permissions
  *Matt Garnes - Add default for Settings.System.DOUBLE_TAP_SLEEP_GESTURE.
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: recalculate clock position on removing empty shade views
  *Andy Mast - Enable fingerprint option in Settings [1/3]
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint [1/2]: Numerous Fingerprint Improvements
  *Roman Birg - density: do not apply to virtual displays
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: hide navigation bar faster in SetupWizard
  *Danny Baumann - Clear callback handler queue when unregistering a phone state listener.
  *d34d - Stop checking for resources.arsc in shouldCreateIdmap
  *Adnan Begovic - frameworks: Factor out Profiles API to CMSDK
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: fix recents task view height calculation
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: don't launch visualizer before we are attached
  *Roman Birg - return default density only for primary display
  *Steve Kondik - alarmmanager: Add sanity checking for elapsed_realtime alarms
  *tobitege - QSTileView: fix label recreate order
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: be more event driven in keyguard visualizer
  *Scott Mertz - Fingerprint: Make the existing FingerprintService semi-useful.
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: workaround for visualizer flash on track change
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: dynamically generate visualizer color
  *Steve Kondik - alarmmanager: Reduce calls to elapsedRealtime()
  *ywen - Fix a GL error leak issue
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: visualizer state improvements
  *STELIX - Fw_Base - Super Slim PIE Fix [1/2]
  *rogersb11 - I like yours better
  *rogersb11 - Add restart systemui to slim actions 2/2
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: SlimPie (1/2) - From BlissRom
  *LorDClockaN - DERP after gazilion patches
  *LorDClockaN - Fix build after slim's shortcuts
  *fusionjack - Framework: SlimAction as QuickTile (1/2)
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: add ability to send a custom intent after keyguard is finished
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: Keyguard - Add user configurable shortcuts
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: add all slim shortcut image resources
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: inital bringup of slim actions and helper classes
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: smart pulldown we do not support anymore
  *Lars Greiss - Frameworks: Add several Slim helper classes and constants back
  *Daniel Koman - frameworks: vectorize slim shortcut action icons
  *dankoman - Frameworks: add shortcut action icons
  *Sven R - Frameworks: moar shortcut icons by Sven R.
  *Danny Baumann - Remove some useless code in KeyguardUpdateMonitor.
  *Danny Baumann - Optimize GPS property reloading.
  *ed.mancebo - Add sms short codes for Indonesia
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: fix dpad arrow keys after rotation
  *Kim Le - Revert "base: zenmode: add 90 minutes downtime"
  *Dave Kover - Fix LiveDisplay notification.
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: fix visualizer tile initial state
  *Andreas Gampe - Frameworks/base: Add removeAll for ArraySet
  *Adnan Begovic - core: Protect against system server take down on empty tile order.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *wangjing - Default time format is hard coded to 24
  *Kra1o5 - Revert "Determine default 12/24 hour time format setting from locale."
  *jrizzoli - base: zenmode: add 90 minutes downtime
  *Andrew Dodd - wifi: Allow Settings to retrieve country code (2/3)
  *Jorge Ruesga - base: wifi priorities
  *Roman Birg - Profiles: fix mute ring mode not applying
  *Steve Kondik - themes: Load icon packs outside the big lock
  *Michael Bestas - Improve dynamic tile strings
  *Jorge Ruesga - base: dynamic tiles
  *Jorge Ruesga - qs: use external resource package for custom tiles
  *jinchul.kim - KillProcessGroup on background thread
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "Kill process asynchronously on updateOomAdjLocked."
  *Charles Tsai - Fix overflow/underflow problem in comparison
  *jinho.park - Fix bug regarding the comparator sorts Alarms into increasing time order.
  *Steve Kondik - am: Fix delayed GC merge damage, again
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: fix navbar dpad arrow keys regression
  *Steve Kondik - themes: Fix strictmode warnings
  *Roman Birg - AudioService: don't launch music player while in call
  *d34d - Close cursor after getting supported components.
  *emancebo - SettingsProvider: turn off mobile data roaming by default
  *Adnan Begovic - PackageManagerService: Don't attempt to dexopt platform-res.
  *d34d - Show reboot dialog using themed resources
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: hide blur when showing keyguard media
  *jie.liu - Properly animate SIM PIN entry screen transition.
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Navigation Bar Customization [1/2]"
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "fix bug about view cache in RemoteViews"
  *d34d - Handle case where profiles.xml was partially saved
  *STELIX - FW_Base - forgot to declare boolean
  *tobitege - Heads Up: Fix heads up default colors, part duh
  *tobitege - Heads Up: no custom text color in power save mode
  *tobitege - FW_Base - Fix default battery text color (2/2)
  *tobitege - Navbar: tint and buttons loading fixup
  *STELIX - Revert "Navbar: tint and buttons loading fixup"
  *tobitege - Fix heads up default colors
  *Corey Edwards - Fix the Chamber Of Secrets
  *d34d - Get themed resources in KeyButtonView
  *tobitege - Status bar header: fix custom buttons long-click
  *tobitege - Navbar: tint and buttons loading fixup
  *tobitege - Navbar loading and tint improvements
  *asianflavor - Fixed back softkey when nav bar height was changed
  *eyosen - notification drawer: powermenu updates
  *tobitege - Fix VPN icon color
  *tobitege - Fix: init notification count text color
  *Kyrylo Mikos - SystemUI: Fix missing top task in recent panel.
  *Alexander Martinz - SystemUI: Keyguard: do not limit double tap to sleep to statusbar
  *Lokesh Chamane - TaskManager: Update some functions
  *Janson Kang - SystemUI: Cleanup longpress action for Heads Up button
  *dexmc - SystemUI: Add longpress action for TaskManager button
  *siracuervo - Enable some more actions for navbar
  *Daniel Koman - SystemUI: vector support for navbar/pie icons
  *westcripp - FW_Base - Improve Task manager UI
  *Altaf-Mahdi - SystemUI: Double tap to sleep anywhere on the lock screen (1/2)
  *westcripp - Task manager : Remove empty notification after switch on/off logic
  *westcripp - Task Manager : On switch recreate statusbar to fix task view
  *Dave Kessler - NavigationBarView: Add image rotation handling for phones
  *Altaf-Mahdi - FW_Base - Task manager improvements: Switch [1/2]
  *Nico60 - Add color to network traffic arrows
  *Daniel Koman - frameworks: vectorize slim shortcut action icons
  *jgcaap - FW_Base - More pratical recents animation timeout
  *Altaf-Mahdi - Base: option to disable torch when the screen turns off (1/2)
  *STELIX - FW_Base - Custom scrolling values: fix the build
  *garwedgess - [1/5] Base: Breathing missedcall/sms/voicemail
  *Yanuar Harry - FW_Base - custom scrolling values [1/2]
  *Dave Kover - SystemUI: Expose values in status bar expanded header
  *Roman Birg - Explicitly declare which permissions can be granted via signature
  *Roman Birg - Allow permissions to be granted via whitelisted signatures
  *Roman Birg - Density scaling: return device's default density
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: don't reinflate search view on rotate
  *Chirayu Desai - Revert "Fixes large number of thumbnails leads to low memory"
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *tobitege - Fix USB intent warning on deviceAttached()
  *Roman Birg - ExternalStorageFormatter: pass whether to wipe internal storage
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *tobitege - Fix USB intent warning on deviceAttached()
  *Roman Birg - ExternalStorageFormatter: pass whether to wipe internal storage
  *STELIX - FW_Base - QS: Fix some tile's animation
  *heydabop - fix build
  *Jet.Z - fix bug about view cache in RemoteViews
  *riddle_hsu - [ActivityManager] Fix index OOB when updating visible.
  *jinchul.kim - Kill process asynchronously on updateOomAdjLocked.
  *riddle_hsu - Run BatteryCallback on CpuTracker thread.
  *emancebo - PackageManagerService: override native lib root for prebundled packages
  *d34d - Add File.separator to end of internalPath
  *Lucas Gomez Jimenez - Fix in effectCallback to avoid sending callbacks to dead objects
  *Jason Monk - Add hotspot icon to status bar
  *Christopher Tate - Close race condition in binderDied()
  *Satish Kodishala - Bluetooth: Adding synchronization to handle multiple threads
  *Steve Kondik - power: Fix locking for wakeup proximity check
  *Arne Coucheron - audio: fix incall music ifdefs (2/3)
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: always log statusbar state
  *Michael Stucki - Revert "frameworks/base: Make minfree values optimal for 32bit devices"
  *Michael Bestas - SystemUI: Add missing QS accessibility messages
  *Dave Kover - SystemUI: Add new dimens values for expanded status bar padding
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Revert "Revert "Boot up optimization for phoneprocess""
  *Danny Baumann - Add a method to query the voicemail number.
  *Stephen Bird - MediaScanner: Detect folders
  *xinhe - Fix for empty RSSI triangle after boot
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: add missed statusbar state logging
  *Roman Birg - Revert "SystemUI: Fix no LED indication for missed call when screen off"
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: remove duplicate PhoneStatusBar variables
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: add RecentsView EventLogs
  *Erica Chang - services: button brightness should check proximity
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Don't set mHomeConsumed to true for KEY_ACTION_SLEEP
  *Erica Chang - frameworks: display: shorten automatic brightness debounce
  *Dave Kover - SystemUI: Expose weather text colors
  *Adnan Begovic - SystemUi: Support expanded styles for custom tiles.
  *nadlabak - PowerManagerService: Fix updating of mUserActivitySummary
  *Roman Birg - Density scaling: scale compatibility apps, wm command support
  *Roman Birg - Revert "Revert "Allow custom density setting""
  *Chris Sarbora - Drop protection level of certain SMS-related system permissions
  *Aditya Pandey - Code Cleanup: No longer required as AOSP commit supersedes this
  *Jinpyo-laptop - Over scroll effects 1/2
  *tobitege - Prevent NPE in InputMethodManager.Map
  *tobitege - Fix navigation bar buttons with custom tint color
  *tobitege - Fix low battery exception with custom Heads Up colors
  *tobitege - Fix Navigation bar custom button sizes
  *Lokesh Chamane - Base: HeadsUp snooze function [1/2]
  *Janson Kang - FW_Base - Update to Heads Up
  *cristianomatos - Update pie icons on theme changes
  *tobitege - Extra null checks; fix vibrate and animations
  *tobitege - Add power menu button transition upon header expansion/collapse
  *Altaf-Mahdi - SystemUI: add HeadsUp button in status bar header (1/2)
  *westcripp - Materialize task kill button
  *Altaf-Mahdi - FW_Base - Changes in Heads up qs tile
  *BigBrother1984 - FW_Base - Improve HeadsUp [1/2]
  *Chet Kener - core: Update GPS Icons to be more Material
  *Lars Greiss - InputWrapper: opt out early if session == null
  *David96 - Fix NPE causing a hot reboot when pressing power button
  *Jostein Kjønigsen - Fix Photosphere/Camera FCs
  *tobitege - Avoid NPE in ArraysAdapter on null item
  *tobitege - Silence chatty TypedArray logging
  *guotao.deng - VolumePanel: volume bar disorderly jump when drag it.
  *longping.zou - MultiSelectListPreference.java should deal with onRestoreInstanceState method
  *d34d - Observer NAVBAR_FORCE_ENABLE in LockTaskNotify
  *William C. Garrison III - VolumePanel: better handling of updating sliders in expanded view
  *William C. Garrison III - VolumePanel: show hint for unlinked notification slider too
  *Andy Mast - Introduce Theme Versioning [1/2]
  *Hamster Tian - frameworks/base: enable localization of Chinese operator's PLMN
  *Scott Mertz - fingerprint: register correct function for nativeEnrollCancel
  *Scott Mertz - fingerprint: detach java vm in HAL callback
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Brandon McAnsh - Profiles: Setup uuid's for the defaults
  *yong.zou - Settings: Fix install apps will fail after setting Preferred install location as Removable SD card and removing SD card
  *Roman Birg - SystemUI: prompt for SIM PIN if lockscreen is disabled
  *Danny Baumann - Fix typo in density assignment.
  *Roman Birg - Revert "Allow custom density setting"
  *tobitege - FW_Base - Fix clock seconds display with am/pm
  *STELIX - Revert "FW_Base - Fix clock seconds display with am/pm"
  *STELIX - FW_Base - Update a string
  *Kryten2k35 - Call recording encoder/format choice 3/3
  *Muhammed Nazim - [3/3] frameworks/base: National Data Roaming
  *darkobas - make lockscreen weather fonts a bit smaller
  *rogersb11 - FW_Base - Power menu header button improvement
  *Kra1o5 - FW_Base - Add option to set default custom function to button recents (1/2)
  *tobitege - Fix NPE in GlobalActions.getUiContext if result is null
  *tobitege - Fix NPE in navbar with ACTION_IME being null
  *Susan McCombs - FW_Base - Fix ForceClose due to TaskManger.
  *haiyangl - FW_Base - SystemUI: Add task manager
  *Andy Mast - Themes: Fix Reboot Background
  *rmcc - Theme reboot menu
  *Daniel MM - CarbonLogo: Increase "C" size
  *Daniel MM - Carbon Easter Egg (1/2)
  *Matt Garnes - Determine default 12/24 hour time format setting from locale.
  *Varad Deshmukh - Modify GC Delay to include subsequent launches. (fix)
  *Roman Birg - Revert "Better density scaling compatibility"
  *Roman Birg - Profiles: re-enable data toggling
  *Roman Birg - Better density scaling compatibility
  *Jorge Ruesga - systemui: notify everyone that lockscreen is not going to be shown
  *rogersb11 - FW_Base - Fix tiles with custom colors toggle issues
  *tobitege - FW_Base - Fix clock seconds display with am/pm
  *AlmightyMegadeth00 - FW_Base - Navigation Bar Customization [1/2]
  *STELIX - FW_Base - SystemUI Recents: just a little cleanUp

Project name: android_frameworks_opt_chips
  *emancebo - chips: extend phone number regex to recognize russian trunk prefix
  *Yvonne Wong - Fix exception that crashes app when <<>> chip is clicked on issue-id: CYNGNOS-522
  *Danesh M - Revert "More Chip: use pendingcount instead of counting again"
  *Stephen Bird - More Chip: use pendingcount instead of counting again
  *Matt Garnes - Apply anti-aliasing when drawing chips.

Project name: android_frameworks_opt_hardware
  *Steve Kondik - cmhw: Add PersistentStorage API
  *Steve Kondik - hardware: Add DisplayModeControl API
  *Steve Kondik - cmhw: Add auto contrast support

Project name: android_frameworks_opt_telephony
  *Adnan Begovic - Telephony: Make sure we're stripping non-digits prior checkDestination.
  *Adnan Begovic - telephony: Fix FrameworksTelephonyTests.
  *Chirayu Desai - Add the user set network mode to the siminfo table
  *Chirayu Desai - Change network mode on data sub change
  *Amit Mahajan - DO NOT MERGE Change to add STK_PERMISSION for stk related commands.
  *emancebo - Telephony: fallback to xml resources for sms shortcode recognition
  *Martin Brabham - [MMS-55]: Add column to interface
  *Muhammed Siju - Fix LTE attach issue due to wrong initial attach profile.
  *emancebo - telephony: read IMSI from CSIM if available in CDMALTEPhone
  *Deepak Kundra - Telephony: Apply SPN override for cdma SIM (RUIM)
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - SIMRecords: Treat empty SPN fields as null and proceed with the fallbacks
  *emancebo - telephony: use IMEI as device ID when LteOnCdma mode is enabled
  *emancebo - msim: fix parse error when roaming with slot 2 only
  *Danny Baumann - Send out a new SPN_STRINGS_UPDATED broadcast if the sub ID changes.
  *Danesh M - Telephony : Ensure private numbers are blocked if block unknown numbers is enabled
  *Beena More - Telephony: DDS switch oemhook message sent twice
  *Muhammed Siju - Fix duplicate events received in DcTracker.
  *Sukanya Rajkhowa - Check for DDS validity
  *Sukanya Rajkhowa - Reject network request when DDS is invalid
  *Susheel nyamala - Telephony: On demand DDS switch uses preferred sub
  *Sukanya Rajkhowa - Ignore DdsRequest for non DDS network factory
  *Muhammed Siju - Fix DDS switch issue from GSM to CDMA.
  *Hu Chunming - Fix issue that DDS can not get back to primary sub and network mode shows incorrect in settings.
  *Lokesh Chamane - Fix the build
  *emancebo - msim: order getSubInfo list by slot ID
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Revert "SubscriptionController: getPhoneId() should never return negative values"
  *Sandeep Gutta - MSIM: Change default fallback subId value
  *Mengjun Leng - Fix ACTION_DEFAULT_SUBSCRIPTION_CHANGED is not sent after power on
  *Adnan - Telephony: Actually abort flex mapping if subs are null.
  *Michael Bestas - Revert "Set default SMS outgoing check interval to 15 minutes"
  *Muhammed Nazim - Return: National Data Roaming [1/3]
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - RIL: Fix datacall parcel reading

Project name: android_frameworks_opt_net_wifi
  *Hu Wang - Wifi: set mConnected true before start monitor thread
  *sanketk - wifi: do not adjust wifi score when WQE is enabled
  *Henrik Baard - Fix memory leak in WifiNative
  *Hu Wang - Wifi: get rid of the log from Gbk2Utf
  *Nalla Kartheek - Wifi:Set framework disconnected state scan interval when P2P connected
  *Jorge Ruesga - wifi: wifi priorities
  *Jorge Ruesga - wifi: Allow Settings to retrieve country code (1/3)

Project name: android_frameworks_av
  *Kyle Repinski - stagefright: id3: Fix crash.
  *Kyle Repinski - Fix compiler issues uncovered at higher optimization levels.
  *Jorge Ruesga - mediascanner: handle DATE tag
  *Dhananjay Kumar - soundpool: update sample rate when reusing audiotrack
  *Dhananjay Kumar - soundpool: reuse channel for same sample if available
  *Satya Krishna Pindiproli - mediaplayerservice: reset mBytesWritten in AudioSink flush and stop
  *Caio Schnepper - stagefright: Correct Exynos4 stride alignment
  *rINanDO - stagefright: Exynos4 MPEG4 decoder should set native color format.
  *Eric Laurent - audio effects: fix heap overflow
  *Andreas Schneider - libstagefright: Add support for NV21 color format
  *Alexy Joseph - libmedia: Increase framecount in Track Offload
  *Christopher R. Palmer - stagefright: Add libhwc to exynos include paths
  *Christopher N. Hesse - stagefright: Add support for Exynos hardware audio decoding
  *Ethan Chen - stagefright: Update makefile for Exynos variants.
  *Narsinga Rao Chella - audiopolicy: fix for voice call to work on USB headset during concurrency
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright: Don't crash on invalid / null AVCC atoms in MKV
  *Mazhar - Fatal error while playing certain mkv files.
  *Nick Kralevich - MPEG4Extractor.cpp: handle chunk_size > SIZE_MAX
  *Zhou Song - AudioMixer: fill 0s at right place when no more buffers available
  *Surajit Podder - video: Disable resync markers
  *Sultanxda - libstagefright: Scale up bitrate for HSR videos
  *Zach Riggle - IOMX: Add buffer range check to emptyBuffer
  *Chong Zhang - HDCP: buffer over flow check -- DO NOT MERGE
  *Marco Nelissen - Add some sanity checks
  *Lajos Molnar - Add AUtils::isInRange, and use it to detect malformed MPEG4 nal sizes
  *Manikanta Kanamarlapudi - libstagefright: Fix incorrect duration calculation
  *Kim Zhang - libstagefright: fix output buffer is not released by Writer when stopping
  *Niel Alejandro Paz - Validation of Number of Channels on WAV files
  *daisuke jinno - The preview frame data is broken when sending via Binder
  *Evgenii Stepanov - Fix new[] vs delete mismatch.
  *Marco Nelissen - Check allocation
  *Evgenii Stepanov - Fix global-buffer-overflow in voAWB_Copy.
  *myfluxi - libstagefright: Remove nBitPerSample CHECK
  *Joshua J. Drake - Detect allocation failures and bail gracefully
  *Nick Kralevich - MPEG4Extractor.cpp: Add check for size == SIZE_MAX
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix null-pointer-dereferences accessing the SampleTable
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix multiple division-by-zero conditions in MPEG4 parsing
  *Dhananjay Kumar - libeffects: validate channel mask in downmixer configure
  *Ashish Jain - audiopolicy: fix playback of multichannel pcm clips via low latency output
  *Mingming Yin - audiopolicy: use deep_buffer as default output for music stream
  *Haynes Mathew George - AudioOutput: Always open AudioTrack with a flag
  *Wei Jia - SampleTable: fix integer overflow checks.
  *Joshua J. Drake - MPEG4Extractor: still more NULL dereference fixes
  *Marco Nelissen - Guard against codecinfo overflow
  *Haynes Mathew George - nuplayer: Fix incorrect state handling while shutting down a decoder
  *Shivaprasad Hongal - libstagefright: Fix crash in convertMetaDataToMessage
  *kunleiz - audiopolicy: Fix for isStateInCall() do not return proper status
  *Apurupa Pattapu - httplive: Adjust seek time to last video IDR time
  *Apurupa Pattapu - httplive: Check for NULL playlist in postPrepared
  *Apurupa Pattapu - httplive: Check for bandwidth switch only for variant playlists
  *Mingming Yin - libstagefright: use SW AAC encoder for HE-AAC format
  *Alexy Joseph - libmedia: Enable TrackOffload for more usecases
  *Alexy Joseph - libmedia: AudioTrack offload only for STREAM_MUSIC
  *Ethan Chen - audiopolicy: Make sense of concurrency properties
  *Michael Bestas - libstagefright: Fix LPA default min duration
  *dianlujitao - audiopolicy: Fix DTS Eagle dependence on kernel
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - cameraservice: Resolve message vs start/stop preview races
  *Dan Pasanen - camera: add ability for a device to specify MAX_CAMERAS
  *Ethan Chen - stagefright: Remove deprecated FFMPEG config
  *Joshua J. Drake - Prevent reading past the end of the buffer in 3GPP
  *Joshua J. Drake - Prevent integer underflow if size is below 6
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix integer overflow when handling MPEG4 tx3g atom
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix integer underflow in covr MPEG4 processing
  *Joshua J. Drake - Prevent integer overflow when processing covr MPEG4 atoms
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright: Move a bunch of FFMPEG stuff out of here
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright: Add support for loading a custom OMXPlugin
  *Ethan Chen - audio: Reduce logging verbosity
  *Paras Nagda - Acodec: Add interlaced video support
  *Pavan Chikkala - audio: fallback to SW decoder for video clips
  *Alexy Joseph - libmedia: restrict nuplayer from using track offload
  *Caio Schnepper - libstagefright: back off exynos4_enhancements HWC_HWOVERLAY usage
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Revert "libstagefright: free mMoovBoxBuffer"
  *Steve Kondik - audiopolicy: Add msm8994
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - stagefright: ffmpeg: Slightly raise the threshold for the ffmpeg scanner
  *Xavier Varricatt - nuplayer: Fix incorrect audio resume time during seek
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright: Fix issues with software decoders
  *Yogesh Solanke - Nuplayer: During flush operation flush audiosink
  *Haynes Mathew George - audiooutput: Serialize access to AudioOutput
  *Sharad Sangle - nuplayer: Don't write data to sink if sink is stopped
  *Arne Coucheron - audiopolicy: Use legacy alsa to guard incall music feature
  *Steve Kondik - audiopolicy: Unbreak incall music
  *Xiaoming Yang - NuPlayer: Clear stale track packets on seek
  *Weiyin Jiang - nuplayer: start or stop audio sink from renderer only
  *Naresh Tanniru - Revert "audio: Reduce device switch delay"
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix integer overflow during MP4 atom processing
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix integer underflow in ESDS processing
  *Joshua J. Drake - Fix several ineffective integer overflow checks
  *Ramjee Singh - audio: removed stream type check from AudioTrack
  *Manikanta Sivapala - nuplayer: improve startup/rebuffering for http progressive playback
  *Amit Shekhar - frameworks/av: Fix NULL check for source
  *Chaithanya Krishna Bacharaju - stagefright: Replace strncpy with strlcpy
  *Preetam Singh Ranawat - NuPlayer: Fix incorrect time update for pause followed by seek, resume
  *Preetam Singh Ranawat - NuPlayer: Fix for pcm offload not using offload path after pause time out
  *Preetam Singh Ranawat - AudioFlinger: Add PCM offload format for dumpsys logging
  *Preetam Singh Ranawat - NuPlayer: Fix for PCM offload fallback on BT
  *lubiny - RTSPSource: check audio buffer count
  *Hui (QRD) Yu - Nuplayer: Fix no image or image will be delay issue
  *Dan Liang - Fix div zero error in corrupted media file
  *Mykola Kondratenko - MediaCodec: use non-blocking call to get service
  *Marco Nelissen - Signal EOS at end of mpeg video to flush out final sample
  *Suresh Choudhary - libstagefright: free mMoovBoxBuffer
  *Marco Nelissen - Don't fail read when "seeking" to current position
  *Robert Shih - ESQueue:use 0x000001 instead of 0x00000001 as sync word in H264/MPEG_VIDEO
  *Arne Coucheron - audio: fix incall music ifdefs (3/3)
  *nadlabak - audiopolicy: Fix call recording for legacy qcom HAL (again)

Project name: android_frameworks_native
  *Dan Stoza - SurfaceFlinger: Fix integer overflow in Mesh ctor
  *Dan Stoza - libgui: Clear frame number while freeing slot
  *Adnan Begovic - native: Move fingerprint feature out of android namespace.
  *Jesse Hall - libagl: Fix buffer read overrun in eglCreatePbufferSurface
  *Ethan Chen - Revert "binder: Remove deprecated Exynos platform variant logic"
  *Ethan Chen - binder: Remove deprecated Exynos platform variant logic
  *Ethan Chen - binder: Update makefile for Exynos variants
  *Adam Lesinski - Verify that the native handle was created
  *radhakrishna - sf: Restrict GPU tile render feature to MAX_LAYER_COUNT
  *Saurabh Shah - SF: Enable context priority
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "Add OMX_AUDIO_CodingAPE and OMX_AUDIO_CodingDTS"
  *Chitti Babu Theegala - Tuning compiler thread count for optimal application install times
  *Dan Stoza - SF: Skip render-to-texture for color transforms
  *Jorge Ruesga - native: dock battery
  *Andy Mast - Enable fingerprint option in Settings [2/3]
  *Jesse Hall - surfaceflinger: use Mutex timedLock instead of tryLock loop
  *Dan Stoza - SF: Reduce resync samples without present
  *bmc08gt - Add dalvik heap override for xxxhdpi phone
  *bmc08gt - Add HWUI overrides for xxxhdpi phone

Project name: android_external_icu
  *Zach Riggle - Fix potential overflow issue
  *Elliott Hughes - Cherrypick http://bugs.icu-project.org/trac/changeset/37162.
  *Roman Birg - Revert "icu: add Kiev meta translations"
  *Roman Birg - icu: add Kiev meta translations
  *Roman Birg - Revert "icu: add Kiev summer time zone translation"
  *Roman Birg - icu: add Kiev summer time zone translation

Project name: freetype
  *Makoto Onuki - Update to freetype 2.6.0
  *Ben Wagner - Add ftmm.c to FreeType build.

Project name: android_external_stagefright-plugins
  *Christopher R. Palmer - ffmpeg-extractor: Fix deadlock when stopping the reader thread
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Restructure the code
  *Ethan Chen - stagefright-plugins: Remove Vorbis/MP3/H263/H264/HEVC
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Fix adaptive buffer and crop handling
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Add special handling of DivX files
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Improve seeking further
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Disable lowres
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Update codec list with capabilities
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Set sensible defaults for audio decoders
  *Steve Kondik - ffmpeg: Remove a couple of codecs we don't need
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Minor fix for FFMPEG 2.7
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Convert tabs to spaces
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Refactoring the extractor
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Clean up makefiles
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Move and update codec XML
  *Steve Kondik - stagefright-plugins: Refactor the decoders
  *Ethan Chen - FFmpegExtractor: mark HEVC as supported

Project name: android_external_lzma
  *Steve Kondik - xz: Enable crc64 support

Project name: conscrypt
  *Kenny Root - OpenSSLX509Certificate: mark mContext as transient

Project name: android_external_sonivox
  *Eric Laurent - DLS parser: fix wave pool size check.
  *Eric Laurent - DLS parser: fix wave pool size check.

Project name: android_external_libpng
  *Narayan Kamath - Restore a width check that was removed from png.c (CVE-2015-0973)

Project name: android_external_bluetooth_bluedroid
  *Łukasz Domeradzki - Fix O3 SIGBUS
  *Markus Schmidt - Bluetooth losing HF connection to car-kit after 5 seconds
  *tobitege - Fix compile error in btif_rfcomm due to invalid comparison
  *Steve Kondik - bluedroid: Fix uninitialized variable warning
  *Christopher R. Palmer - bluetooth: a2dp: Property account pcm.counter
  *Christopher R. Palmer - bluetooth: a2dp: Allow 2 full tick's worth of data to be sent
  *Christopher R. Palmer - bluetooth: a2dp: Buffer sufficient data to keep devices happy

Project name: android_external_openssl
  *Brandon McAnsh - openssl: host: Only show warning if HOST OS is not linux or darwin

Project name: android_external_wpa_supplicant_8
  *Scott Mertz - Revert "eap_peer: add more qmi dependencies with qmi proxy"
  *Scott Mertz - eap_peer: add more qmi dependencies with qmi proxy
  *Jouni Malinen - P2P: Validate SSID element length before copying it
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - eap_peer: Make the QMI EAP proxy a standalone lib
  *Jouni Malinen - EAP-pwd server: Fix payload length validation for Commit and Confirm
  *Jouni Malinen - EAP-pwd server: Fix Total-Length parsing for fragment reassembly
  *Jouni Malinen - EAP-pwd peer: Make sure in_frag_pos is cleared to zero on allocation.
  *Jouni Malinen - EAP-pwd peer: Fix asymmetric fragmentation behavior.
  *Jouni Malinen - EAP-pwd peer: Fix Total-Length parsing for fragment reassembly.
  *Jouni Malinen - EAP-pwd peer: Fix payload length validation for Commit and Confirm.
  *Jouni Malinen - AP WMM: Fix integer underflow in WMM Action frame parser.
  *Jouni Malinen - WPS: Check maximum HTTP body length earlier in the process.
  *Jouni Malinen - WPS: Extra validation step for HTTP reader
  *Jouni Malinen - WPS: Fix HTTP chunked transfer encoding parser.

Project name: android_external_f2fs-tools
  *Keith Mok - Fix f2fs_trim_device multiple definitions
  *Keith Mok - Add darwin support for building the host tools
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: don't need to limit MIN_VOLUME SIZE
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: set overprovision size more precisely
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: fix wrong documentation
  *Yunlei He - fsck.f2fs: add segment type in sit_dump
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: drop extent_info to avoid potential wrong access
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: select to update the latest valid summary
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: add hash conversion for encrypted dentries
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: avoid build warning
  *Jaegeuk Kim - dump.f2fs: show i_advise field in inode
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: show superblock features and encryption info
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: set encryption feature
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: show ckeckpoint version info
  *Jaegeuk Kim - Revert "mkfs.f2fs: 512 UTF-16 characters for label"
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: fix orphan inode's link count
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: fix missing dentries
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: clean up child information
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: fix missing i_links
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: count child directories correctly for i_links
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: fix corrupted dentries
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: fix summary block
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: return summary block pointer and types
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: preserve orphan blocks
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: skip block count fix when i_links is fixed
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: fix inodes having wrong i_links
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: check file types
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: remove inconsistent named directories
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: reduce redundant message
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: 512 UTF-16 characters for label
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: add quite mode, -q
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: show total sectors consumed by filesystem
  *Jaegeuk Kim - fsck.f2fs: show cp_state for fsck.f2fs
  *Jaegeuk Kim - mkfs.f2fs: show bytes for total_sectors
  *Gustavo Zacarias - configure: add check for fallocate
  *Anthony G. Basile - f2fs-tools: fix build system to make distcheck correctly

Project name: android_external_ffmpeg
  *dhacker29 - ffmpeg: Set cpu arch for silvermont config
  *Steve Kondik - ffmpeg: Readd missing X86 fixups
  *Steve Kondik - ffmpeg: Regenerate configurations for FFMPEG 2.7
  *Steve Kondik - ffmpeg: Add script to regenerate the configs
  *Steve Kondik - ffmpeg: Update Android build configuration
  *dhacker29 - x86: Use yasm from prebuilts and don't depend on host install
  *Howard M. Harte - Add configuration for silvermont CPU based on Atom.
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Clean up some build-time warnings
  *Chris Sarbora - Get ffmpeg building for emulatorx86
  *Steve Kondik - ffmpeg: Fix variable collisions
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - build: Use ARM mode for arm32 builds
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Fixup armv8-a building, and make multiarch builds work
  *Steve Kondik - avutil: Use _SC_NPROCESSORS_CONF
  *Steve Kondik - Update Android build for FFMPEG 2.5
  *Chih-Wei Huang - Android porting for ffmpeg 2.1 release
  *Michael Niedermayer - configure: Disable VSX on unspecified / generic CPUs
  *Deliang Fu - avformat: Fix bug in parse_rps for HEVC.
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - takdec: ensure chan2 is a valid channel index
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/h264_slice: Use AVFrame diemensions for grayscale handling
  *Michael Niedermayer - avdevice/lavfi: do not rescale AV_NOPTS_VALUE in lavfi_read_packet()
  *Michael Niedermayer - MAINTAINERS: add 2.7
  *Michael Niedermayer - Update for 2.7
  *Michael Niedermayer - add RELEASE_NOTES, based on previous
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - sonic: set avctx->channels in sonic_decode_init
  *Michael Niedermayer - Changelog: Add 2.7 entry
  *Michael Niedermayer - doc/APIchanges: fill in missing stuff
  *Michael Niedermayer - doc/APIchanges: Add 2.7 separator
  *Simon Thelen - libavutil/channel_layout: Correctly return layout when channel specification ends with a trailing 'c'.
  *Vignesh Venkatasubramanian - lavf/webm_chunk: Remove AVFMT_ALLOW_FLUSH
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Fix gain regression with gray16
  *Michael Niedermayer - fate: Force jpeg2000 decoder for dcinema
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/libopenjpegdec: Mark as experimental if <= 1.3
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000: remove unused variable
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/oggenc: Fix return code in case of flushing
  *Rodger Combs - doc/muxers: document new break_non_keyframes option
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000: Disable special case for JPEG2000_QSTY_SI
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Add placeholder for PLT parsing
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Handle Psot = 0
  *Luca Barbato - mkv: Correctly report the latest packet had been flushed
  *Rodger Combs - lavf/segment: add an option to allow breaking on non-keyframes
  *James Almer - mpjpegdec: don't try to alloc an AVIOContext when probe is guaranteed to fail
  *Janne Grunau - imc: add required padding for GetBitContext buffer
  *Janne Grunau - ac3_parser: add required padding for GetBitContext buffer
  *Janne Grunau - aac_parser: add required padding for GetBitContext buffer
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/x86/h264_weight: handle weight1=128
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Fix some 5/3 bitexactness issues
  *Rodger Combs - lavf/tls_securetransport: fix SNI support when not verifying
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Fix subsampled decoding
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Check that coords match before applying ICT
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/jpeg2000dec: Fix high bit depth branch sample shift
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - vp8: change mv_{min,max}.{x,y} type to int
  *James Almer - mpjpegdec: don't try to alloc an AVIOContext when probe is guaranteed to fail
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - vp9: change type of tile_size from unsigned to int64_t
  *James Almer - mpjpegdec: fix memory leak in probe function
  *Michael Niedermayer - swr: Fix ASSERT_LEVEL warning
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/hq_hqa: Fix signness of tag
  *Donny Yang - avcodec/apng: Add partial support for blending with PAL8 pixel format
  *Donny Yang - avcodec/apng: Add support for blending with GRAY8A pixel format
  *Donny Yang - avcodec/apng: Add blending support for non-alpha pixel formats
  *Donny Yang - avcodec/apng: Dispose previous frame properly
  *Rodger Combs - lavf/tls: let the user specify what name to verify against
  *Vittorio Giovara - rtpdec_asf: Check memory allocation and free memory on error
  *Vittorio Giovara - mov: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - jack: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - audiointerleave: Always initialize new_pkt
  *Vittorio Giovara - sctp: Always initialize outmsg struct
  *Janne Grunau - mpjpgdec: free AVIOContext leak on early probe fail
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Move OutFormat enum to mpegutils.h
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Split picture allocation for encoding and decoding
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Rework frame_size_alloc function
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Move various temporary buffers to a separate context
  *Luca Barbato - configure: Support MSVC 2015
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mxfenc: Allow overriding /manual setting of the signal standard
  *Max Poliakovski - atrac3plus: give the phase_shift flag a better name.
  *Max Poliakovski - atrac3plus: add support for GHA phase inversion.
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/version: Bump version for single jpeg muxer
  *Michael Niedermayer - doc/ffserver: Add entry for missing jpeg variant
  *Caligula useraccount - ffserver: Use singlejpeg muxer for jpeg
  *Caligula useraccount - avformat: Add single jpeg muxer
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/aacdec: Do not return a uninitialized value
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/hdsenc: Change duration from single to to double precision
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/rmenc: Remove float usage
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/libstagefright: Check for pthread_create() failure
  *Clément Bœsch - avfilter: fix a few 5 spaces indent
  *Michael Niedermayer - avdevice/iec61883: Check pthread init for failures
  *Michael Niedermayer - ffserver: Check for ffio_set_buf_size() failure
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/aviobuf: Check for ffio_set_buf_size() failure
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/ffmdec: Check ffio_set_buf_size() return value
  *Michael Niedermayer - ffserver: Check allocations (likely not all)
  *Luca Barbato - aac: Wait to know the channels before allocating frame
  *Sebastian Dröge - aac: Support channel configurations 11 and 12
  *nu774 - aac: correctly map 7.1ch-wide AAC from FDK AAC encoder
  *Luca Barbato - avio: Add avio_put_str16be
  *Luca Barbato - mpjpeg: Initial implementation
  *James Almer - fate: add missing avdevice dependency to closed caption test
  *Philip Langdale - avcodec/allcodecs: Re-order nvenc encoders below x264/5.
  *Ganesh Ajjanagadde - vf_colormatrix: calculate coefficients only once
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/mpegvideo: Use av_memdup() for allocating thread_context
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/mpegvideo: Clear thread_context array before allocating
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/mpegvideo: Merge thread context initialization loops
  *Philip Langdale - avcodec/nvenc: Add 'nvenc_h264' as an alternative name for 'nvenc'
  *Philip Langdale - avcodec/nvenc: Rename nvenc_h265 to nvenc_hevc
  *Philip Langdale - Revert "avcodec: Rename nvenc.c to nvenc_a.c, to avoid conflict with the other implementation"
  *Philip Langdale - Revert "Merge commit 'b08caa87c35a768ec0abb16b1e99c3a85f1df28e'"
  *Philip Langdale - Revert "nvenc: remove cuda.h requirement for nvenc_a"
  *Philip Langdale - Revert "avcodec/Makefile: fix checkheaders for nvenc_b"
  *Philip Langdale - Revert "Changelog: Drop duplicate NVENC entry"
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/colorspace: Remove RGB_TO_Y/U/V
  *Paul B Mahol - avcodec/exr: fix crash caused by merge
  *James Almer - configure: improve the checks for gmtime_r and localtime_r
  *Michael Niedermayer - Changelog: Drop duplicate NVENC entry
  *Clément Bœsch - avdevice/x11grab: use av_clip() instead of nested min & max
  *Clément Bœsch - avcodec/snowenc: use av_clip() instead of nested min & max
  *Clément Bœsch - avcodec/mpegvideo: use av_clip() instead of nested min & max
  *Clément Bœsch - ffplay: use av_clip() instead of nested min & max
  *Ronald S. Bultje - hevc: fix typo (mpv -> mvp).
  *Clément Bœsch - swresample: fix initilaize/initialize typo
  *Clément Bœsch - doc/filters: fix inaccuarte/inaccurate typo
  *Stephan Holljes - lavf/http: Add simple autodetection for client HTTP method, based on AVIO_FLAG_READ.
  *Stephan Holljes - lavf/http: Indent else-clause.
  *Stephan Holljes - lavf/http: Properly process HTTP header on listen.
  *Stephan Holljes - lavf/http: Rudimentary error handling for HTTP requests received from clients.
  *Stephan Holljes - lavf/http: Process HTTP header before sending response.
  *Stephan Holljes - lavf/http: Document method option.
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mxfenc: Add mxf muxer avclass
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/s302m: Only set the sample rate when some data is output
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/utils: Do not select audio streams with unknown sample rate in av_find_best_stream()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/s302m: Check for non PCM Streams
  *Ganesh Ajjanagadde - flvdec: fix lack of duration for some files
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/flvdec: Show unknown tags at debug level
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/flvdec: Add TYPE_ONCAPTIONINFO
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/flvdec: increase buffer size for parsing metadata string key
  *Michael Niedermayer - Revert addition of a few fixed_dsp functions to APIChanges
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/ppc/cpu: add include avassert.h
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/softfloat: Fix alternative implementation of av_normalize1_sf()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/softfloat: Fix alternative implementation of av_normalize_sf()
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - arm: only enable setend on ARMv6
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/softfloat: Move av_sincos_sf() from header to c file
  *Nedeljko Babic - libavutil/doc: Changes in documentation due to changes to fixed_dsp
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/softfloat: Add more tests for the normalization
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/softfloat: Fix thresholds in av_normalize_sf()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/rdft: Use more specific error codes
  *Vignesh Venkatasubramanian - lavf/matroskaenc: Write Block Keyframe correctly
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/utils: Assert that audio decoders do not report using more data than was input
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/alsdec: Check for overread
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/atrac3plusdec: consume only as many bytes as available
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/adpcm: Check for overreads
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: MSA (MIPS-SIMD-Arch) optimizations for HEVC idct functions
  *Nedeljko Babic - libavutil/softfloat: Fix av_normalize1_sf bias.
  *Juanjo - lavf/riffenc: Set correct block align for mp2.
  *Carl Eugen Hoyos - lavfi/tinterlace: Double aspect ratio for modes merge and pad.
  *Michael Niedermayer - swresample/resample: fix typos
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/proresenc_anatoliy: Use more specific error codes
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/snow: replace unspecific error code
  *Michael Niedermayer - swresample/swresample: Cleanup on init failure.
  *Michael Niedermayer - swresample: Add swr_get_out_samples()
  *James Almer - fate: add missing lavfi indev dependency to closed caption test
  *Michael Niedermayer - libswresample/rematrix: Check for malloc errors
  *Anshul Maheshwari - fate: Add Closed caption test
  *Nedeljko Babic - libavutil: Add new fixed dsp functions.
  *Michael Niedermayer - Revert "avformat/rtpenc: check av_packet_get_side_data() return, fix null ptr dereference"
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: MSA (MIPS-SIMD-Arch) optimizations for HEVC uni mc epel functions
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: MSA (MIPS-SIMD-Arch) optimizations for HEVC mc epel functions
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: MSA (MIPS-SIMD-Arch) optimizations for HEVC biw mc functions
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/ppc/cpu: Our code assumes vsx implies altivec, thus assert this
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mov: Retry same packet on IO failure to avoid loosing a packet
  *Stefano Sabatini - ffmpeg_dxva2: call GetDesktopWindow() in place of GetShellWindow()
  *nu774 - aac: Correctly map multichannel ADTS AAC with non-zero channel_config + PCE
  *Paul B Mahol - avfilter/vf_blend: add linearlight and glow mode
  *Luca Barbato - bink: Factorize bink put_pixel
  *Martin Storsjö - configure: Check for DXVA2_ConfigPictureDecode instead of LPDIRECT3DSURFACE9
  *Martin Storsjö - configure: Remove unnecessary tests for d3d11va
  *Martin Storsjö - configure: Don't run "export $e" for an empty string
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: MSA (MIPS-SIMD-Arch) optimizations for HEVC uniw mc functions
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mxfenc: Accept MXF D-10 with 49.999840 Mbit/sec
  *Ganesh Ajjanagadde - swresample/dither: check memory allocation
  *Donny Yang - avcodec/apng: Remove blending support for AV_PIX_FMT_ARGB
  *Michael Niedermayer - swresample: Check the return value of resampler->init()
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - libopenjpegdec: register logging callback functions
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - libopenjpegenc: use variable instead of type for sizeof
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - libopenjpegenc: add NULL check for img before accessing it
  *Michael Niedermayer - configure: Remove now redundant vsx setting code
  *James Almer - configure: don't enable tls protocols if network is disabled
  *Paul B Mahol - avfilter/vf_blend: add hardmix mode
  *Paul B Mahol - avfilter/vf_blend: fix vividlight blend mode
  *Paul B Mahol - avfilter/vf_blend: clip result for divide blend mode
  *Michael Niedermayer - configure: Do not dump the whole environment to stdout
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/sbgdec: Check alloc_array_elem() return value
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/flacenc: Simplify sizeof()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/proresenc_anatoliy: Check av_frame_alloc() return code
  *Michael Niedermayer - compat/os2threads: Check av_malloc() return code
  *Michael Niedermayer - ffserver: check return code of avio_alloc_context()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mxfdec: return error instead of segfaulting if there are no streams
  *周晓勇 - avcodec: loongson3 optimized h264chroma put and avg with mmi
  *Luca Barbato - configure: Use pkg-config for fdk-aac
  *Luca Barbato - configure: Provide an option to override the environment
  *Luca Barbato - configure: Support the extended pkgconf syntax
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: MSA (MIPS-SIMD-Arch) optimizations for HEVC bi mc functions
  *James Almer - configure: don't enable any tls protocol if network is disabled
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/snowenc: avoid floats in the rangecoder initialization
  *Martin Storsjö - configure: Remove some unnecessary exported config items
  *Martin Storsjö - configure: Require LPDIRECT3DSURFACE9 for dxva2
  *Martin Storsjö - dxva2: Add ifdefs around structs that might not be available
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/rangecoder: avoid float operation
  *James Almer - avcodec/Makefile: fix checkheaders for nvenc_b
  *Stefano Sabatini - doc/formats.texi: document max_interlave_delta muxing option
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/movenc: Fix potential signed overflows
  *Ronald S. Bultje - vp9: clamp final zero MV if find_ref_mvs() found no suitable candidates.
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/float_dsp: Fix ambiguous wording about vector products
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mxfenc: Correct klv_fill_key
  *Steve Lhomme - dxva2: Fix build when only D3D11 or DXVA2 is used
  *Steve Lhomme - configure: Check if ID3D11VideoDecoder exists, not just the header to enable d3d11va
  *Michael Niedermayer - h264: Fix HWACCEL_MAX for D3D11
  *Michael Niedermayer - hevc: Fix HWACCEL_MAX for D3D11
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Use GMP functions directly, instead of nettle wrappers
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Fix the indentation in a struct
  *James Almer - nvenc: remove cuda.h requirement for nvenc_a
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/ppc/pixblockdsp: Fix type of get_pixels_vsx()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/ppc/cpu: Remove !ARCH_PPC64 check for mfspr, the code should now support ppc64
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/utils: Simplify get_std_framerate() check
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec: Rename nvenc.c to nvenc_a.c, to avoid conflict with the other implementation
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/aacpsy: Clear the correct pointer
  *James Almer - x86: check for AV_CPU_FLAG_AVXSLOW where useful
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/ppc/float_dsp_init: Disable duplicate functions
  *Michael Niedermayer - configure: ldbrx seems not working on qemu power8, disable for now
  *Michael Niedermayer - avutil/ppc/cpu: Check if unistd.h is available before including it
  *Gilles Chanteperdrix - avformat/libquvi: fix error handling
  *Luca Barbato - nvenc: H264 and HEVC encoders
  *Vittorio Giovara - xsub: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - wma: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - truemotion2: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - svq1: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - ratecontrol: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - pthread: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - psymodel: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - xvid: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - x264: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - libtheora: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - lcl: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - jpegls: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - huffyuv: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - eatgv: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - dct: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - asv: Check memory allocation
  *Vittorio Giovara - aacpsy: Check memory allocation
  *Peter Cordes - avfilter/vf_mpdecimate: add comment about 8x8 SAD
  *Peter Cordes - avfilter/vf_mpdecimate: support more pixel formats, including GBRP
  *Peter Cordes - avfilter/vf_mpdecimate: debug logging of threshold stats
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Move MotionEstContext and function declarations to a separate header
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: mpeg12: Move function declarations
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Move tables to a separate file
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: msmpeg4: Move function declarations
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: wmv2: Move function declarations
  *Hendrik Leppkes - dxva2_hevc: re-write reference frame handling
  *Hendrik Leppkes - dxva2_hevc: fix 32x32 scaling lists
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - mov: always check avio_read return value
  *Vittorio Giovara - avio: Add avio_read wrapper to simplify error checking
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - mov: reject zero bytes_per_frame with non-zero samples_per_frame
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - mov: abort on EOF in ff_mov_read_chan
  *Luca Barbato - mov: Correctly allocate ctts_data
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - mov: Fix two memleaks
  *Peter Cordes - avfilter/vf_mpdecimate: pass the same AVClass context as use elsewhere to av_pixelutils_get_sad_fn()
  *Vittorio Giovara - vp9: Parse subsampling and report missing feature
  *Clément Bœsch - tests: add some ASS/SSA/MKS remux and transcode tests
  *James Almer - x86: check for AV_CPU_FLAG_AVXSLOW where useful
  *James Almer - x86: Add helper macros to check for slow cpuflags
  *James Almer - x86: add AV_CPU_FLAG_AVXSLOW flag
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: vsx: Implement diff_pixels and get_pixels
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: vsx: Implement float_dsp
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: cpu: Add support for VSX and POWER8 extensions
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: Restrict some Altivec implementations to Big Endian
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: configure: Support ISA 2.06 and later
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: Clarify and extend the cpuid check
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: linux: Check altivec using the auxv
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: pixblockdsp: Use the abriged vector types
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: avutil: Use the abriged vector types
  *Luca Barbato - ppc: avutil: Drop a potentially dangerous workaround
  *Rodger Combs - configure: Check for SecItemImport for securetransport as well
  *wm4 - network: prevent SIGPIPE on OSX
  *Michael Niedermayer - avfilter/vf_fade: Force alpha pixel format if alpha is set to 1
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/parser: Print an error in case of reallocation fails in ff_combine_frame()
  *Michael Niedermayer - postproc: Avoid floats in maxClipped computation
  *Michael Niedermayer - postproc/postprocess_template: Compute packedYScale and QPCorrecture without floats
  *wm4 - network: prevent SIGPIPE on OSX
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - libopenjpegdec: check existence of image component data
  *Michael Niedermayer - doc/ffmpeg: Document xerror
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/movenc: Add loction/xyz support to allow copying data between mov files
  *Luca Barbato - h264: Make sure reinit failures mark the context as not initialized
  *Luca Barbato - msrle: Use FFABS to determine the frame size in msrle_decode_pal4
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mov: Also export loci altitude
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mov: Append place name instead of overwriting for loci
  *Rodger Combs - lavf/tls_securetransport: add missing copyright notice
  *banastasov - avcodec/dvbsubdec: Fix buf_size check in dvbsub_parse_display_definition_segment()
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/h264dec: Add ff_tlog() with trace information about h264 probing
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/h264dec: Fix detection of invalid h264 with 0x100 startcodes
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Generate the whole private exponent using av_get_random_seed() with nettle/gmp
  *Rodger Combs - lavf/tls: Support Secure Transport
  *Michael Niedermayer - configure: Fix showcqt fft dependancy
  *Ingo Brückl - build: add configure option pkgconfigdir
  *Nedeljko Babic - libavutil: Cosmetic changes to fixed_dsp file.
  *Andreas Cadhalpun - mov: fix DTS calculation for samples with negative stts duration
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/mpegvideo: Use FFSWAP to exchange pointers
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/ac3_parser: Avoid floats in bitrate computation
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/movenc: Check that track_width_1616 fits within the available 32bit before storing it
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/movenc: avoid floats in width/height/aspect ratio computations
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/concatdec: Enable auto_convert by default
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mov: Avoid float usage in yuv_to_rgba()
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Create sufficiently long private keys for gcrypt/nettle
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Remove an unnecessary check in the gcrypt/nettle dh_compute_key
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Add fate test for the DH handshake routine
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Pass the actual buffer size of the output secret key
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Check the output buffer size in the openssl version of dh_compute_key
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Fix a local variable name in the nettle/gcrypt codepath
  *Martin Storsjö - rtmpdh: Make sure ret is initialized in the nettle version of bn_hex2bn
  *Hendrik Leppkes - dxva2_hevc: re-write reference frame handling
  *Hendrik Leppkes - dxva2_hevc: fix 32x32 scaling lists
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/mpegvideo: Reset bitstream_buffer_size on allocation failure
  *Roman Savchenko - avcodec/mpegvideo: Check pointer when allocation fail
  *Roman Savchenko - avformat/avienc: Correct possible dereference of null
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips/hevcdsp_msa: Restructure as per avutil/mips/generic_macros_msa.h
  *wm4 - pixfmt: remove misleading and broken documentation
  *Michael Niedermayer - x86: cavs: Remove an unneeded scratch buffer
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: Split uni mc optimizations to new file
  *Anton Khirnov - rl: Add error checking to ff_rl_init().
  *Anton Khirnov - rl: Add a function for freeing dynamically allocated tables.
  *Anton Khirnov - rl: Rename ff_*_rl() to ff_rl_*()
  *Anton Khirnov - mpegvideo: Move ff_*_rl functions to a separate file
  *Vittorio Giovara - mpegvideo: Drop exchange_uv() function and use its code directly
  *wm4 - dvdsubdec: implement flushing
  *wm4 - dvdsubdec: reset buffer size on invalid over-large packets
  *Martin Storsjö - tls_gnutls: Add missing includes for the gcrypt thread safety callbacks
  *Michael Niedermayer - avformat/mxfenc: Support storing signal standard for D10 muxing
  *Carl Eugen Hoyos - lavc/x264: Support bgr0 as input pix_fmt.
  *Carl Eugen Hoyos - lavf: Use av_codec_get_tag2() in avformat_query_codec().
  *Shivraj Patil - avcodec/mips: Restructure as per avutil/mips/generic_macros_msa.h
  *Timothy Gu - x86inc: Clear __SECT__
  *Shivraj Patil - avutil/mips: Restructure of generic macros
  *Timothy Gu - network: Move variable declaration under an #if
  *Michael Niedermayer - avcodec/ffv1dec: Fix skip_alpha
  *Timothy Gu - x86inc: Clear __SECT__
  *Timothy Gu - Revert "Move struc FFTContext below SECTION_RODATA"
  *wm4 - lavf: move TLS-related ifdeffery to library specific files
  *wm4 - lavf: split tls.c

Project name: android_external_libnfc-nci
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - pn547: Don't attempt to downgrade firmware
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - pn547: Force rewrite of config even if we think it's the same
  *Steve Kondik - libnfc-nci: Add NXP chip type disambiguation
  *Jizhou Liao - Rename NXP HAL
  *Rashed Abdel-Tawab - Include stl symbols and headers
  *Jizhou Liao - Update .conf file
  *Jizhou Liao - Add Peer-To-Peer priority mechanism
  *Jizhou Liao - Adding MiFARE DESFire format support
  *Jizhou Liao - Correct corrupted CC value on MIFARE ULC tag
  *Jizhou Liao - T1T HR0 and HR1 parameters missing in tag dectection
  *Jizhou Liao - Increase maximum AID routing buffer length and entry size.
  *Jizhou Liao - Increase APDU buffer size to support extended APDU
  *Jizhou Liao - Fix unhandled NCI errors and wrong states
  *Jizhou Liao - Increase HCI EVT buffer size
  *Jizhou Liao - Fix maximum HCP package size
  *Jizhou Liao - Memory leak and NULL pointer check fixes
  *Jizhou Liao - Code inspection fixes
  *Jizhou Liao - Changes base on coding conventions rules
  *Shareef Ali - Fix board-specific HAL module naming
  *Steve Kondik - nfc_nci: Allow passing in the HAL suffix as a variable
  *Jizhou Liao - Add NFC-DEP routing

Project name: android_external_libtar
  *Tom Marshall - libtar: Support transparent compression

Project name: android_external_dhcpcd
  *Tom Marshall - dhcpcd: Send unique IAID
  *Tom Marshall - dhcpcd: Send proper DUID

Project name: android_external_chromium_org_third_party_boringssl_src
  *kenshin - mitigate logjam (CVE-2015-4000)

Project name: android_external_chromium_org
  *Adam Langley - net: disable SSLv3.

Project name: external_android_support-prebuilt
  *Raj Yengisetty - Update support libs to 22.2.1
  *Stephen Bird - Initial commit
  *Abhisek Devkota - Initial empty repository

Project name: android_external_sepolicy
  *Adnan Begovic - sepolicy: Remove profiles from context, moved to cm
  *Stephen Smalley - Define types for userdata and cache block devices.
  *Manu Prasad - Revert "WFD : Adding policy exceptions in app domain for wfd"
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - domain: Restore original neverallow rules for shipping builds

Project name: android_external_android-visualizer
  *Roman Birg - VisualizerView: add ability to disable drawing
  *Roman Birg - Revert "visualizer: don't draw fade out paint when there's no content"
  *Roman Birg - visualizer: don't draw fade out paint when there's no content
  *Roman Birg - visualizer view: optimize allocations during drawing

Project name: android_external_whispersystems_WhisperPush
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Brinly Taylor - WhisperPush: Update Terms Of Service and Privacy URL
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - WhisperPush: accept registration SMS from any number
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - WhisperPush: add weekly active users metric
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - WhisperPush: service for WPv2 update to interrogate/disable v1
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - WhisperPush: add Twilio SMS number for Indonesia
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *tobitege - Do not launchGcmRegistration if never registered
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_external_whispersystems_curve25519-java
  *Adnan Begovic - curve25519: Make sure we're building the libcurve JNI.
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - curve25519: prevent dex2oat method verify failure

Project name: android_external_whispersystems_TextSecure
  *Adnan Begovic - TextSecure: Deprecate old curve25519.

Project name: android_external_jpeg
  *Xin Qi - Enable neon optimization for 32bits.

Project name: android_kernel_xiaomi_armani
  *tarun93 - update and add carbon kernel defconfig
  *Blechd0se - cpufreq: freq_table: bail out early if freq = target_freq
  *Stratos Karafotis - cpufreq: Introduce new relation for freq selection
  *Alin - security: force SELinux permissive mode
  *tarun93 - Defconfig Update
  *faux123 - mdss_dsi_panel.c: add powersuspend hooks
  *yank555-lu - kernel/power/powersuspend: cumulative update to version 1.5
  *yank555-lu - kernel/power/powersuspend: LCD screen on/off hooks (Yank555.lu)
  *Paul Reioux - kernel/power/powersuspend: default to userspace for now
  *yank555-lu - kernel/power/powersuspend: add back userpace control w/ default kernel control
  *yank555-lu - kernel/power/powersuspend: remove userspace dependency from powersuspend
  *Paul Reioux - powersuspend: fix logci derps :p
  *Paul Reioux - powersuspend: new PM kernel driver for Android w/o early_suspend
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: Fix logic and rectify Alucard parameters
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: Add Alucard hotplug
  *Blechd0se - cpufreq: implement cpufreq_quick_get_util()
  *Joe Maples - Optimize slub by not using fair sleepers
  *Randy DuCharme - Revamp spinlock ASM code
  *Luka Karinja - msm8226: underclock GPU to 100MHz
  *myfluxi - PM: devfreq: Fix show available freqs
  *myfluxi - PM: devfreq: Use high priority workqueue
  *myfluxi - msm: kgsl: Report correct GPU frequency in sysfs
  *tarun93 - drop unwanted things
  *xiaobing tu - deadline: Allow 0ms deadline latency, increase the read speed
  *savoca - msm: mdss: Remove deprecated __dev* markings
  *savoca - msm: mdss: Add pa_v2 support to KCAL
  *savoca - msm: mdss: Replace PGC implementation with PCC for KCAL
  *savoca - msm: mdss: Add KCAL support for post processing control [v2]
  *Luka Karinja - msm: kgsl: build only a3xx for armani, remove a2xx
  *myfluxi - msm: acpuclock: Fix acpuclk_get_rate
  *savoca - drivers: Upgrade frandom from staging
  *savoca - staging: frandom: Clear up checkpatch conflicts
  *savoca - staging: frandom: Dynamically allocate the char device numbers
  *savoca - staging: Add frandom RNG driver
  *faux123 - overall_stats: forward port to kernel 3.4+
  *faux123 - overall_stats: make dual/quad core stats configurable via meunconfig
  *faux123 - overall_stats: add overall stats for all available cores
  *Paul Reioux - Asynchronous Fsync: initial extraction of Async Fsync from HTC
  *Paul Reioux - fs/dyn_sync_cntrl: dynamic sync control
  *Steve Kondik - msm: Fix high load average from uninterruptible waits
  *Angelo G. Del Regno -- EternityProject Team Manager - sched: LOAD_FREQ (4*HZ+61) avoids loadavg Moire
  *poondog - DRIVERS: SLIMBUS: slimbus enhancements mkII
  *tarunkapadia93 - mmc: disable crc check for 30% extra performance in IO
  *Stephen Smalley - selinux: Report permissive mode in avc: denied messages.
  *Steven Rostedt - SELinux: Fix possible NULL pointer dereference in selinux_inode_permission()
  *Eric Paris - SELinux: include definition of new capabilities
  *tarun93 - kgsl : default clock to min clock
  *tarunkapadia93 - .gitingore
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: use of swp{b} is deprecated for ARMv6+ for msm8226
  *tarunkapadia93 - defconfig update
  *tarunkapadia93 - fix cpufreq_interactive.c
  *tarunkapadia93 - msm: hotplug fix derps
  *tarunkapadia93 - Revert "stop_machine: fix race when queue work to stopper thread"
  *tarun93 - fix -Wmaybe-uninitialized errors
  *tarunkapadia93 - compilation fixes
  *Viresh Kumar - cpufreq: Manage only online cpus
  *Viresh Kumar - cpufreq: Move get_cpu_idle_time() to cpufreq.c
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: Add Bricked Hotplug driver
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: msm_rq_stats: Add hotplug enable toggle
  *myfluxi - msm: rq_stats: Calculate load based on current freq limit
  *tarunkapadia93 - msm: Add Intelli Hotplug driver
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: Add MSM hotplug driver
  *Pranav Vashi - drivers: Add state notifier driver
  *kairi_zeroblade - GPU Overclock for MSM8226
  *Jason Hrycay - ARM: module: add text.unlikely section to unwind
  *Colin Cross - ARM: unwind: enable dumping stacks for SMP && ARM_UNWIND
  *Colin Cross - ARM: stacktrace: enable dumping stacks for SMP && FRAME_POINTER
  *Will Deacon - ARM: 7663/1: perf: fix ARMv7 EVTYPE_MASK to include NSH bit
  *Zhi-Ming Yuan - stop_machine: fix race when queue work to stopper thread
  *Se Hun Kim - msm: mdss: Adding lcd notifier
  *Hong-Mei Li - staging: android: lowmemorykiller: implement task's adj rbtree
  *kairi_zeroblade - Update wireless regulatory domain database
  *Behan Webster - ARM: 8158/1: LLVMLinux: use static inline in ARM ftrace.h
  *Sasha Levin - kernel: add support for gcc 5
  *Viresh Kumar - cpufreq: interactive: Remove unnecessary cpu_online() check
  *myfluxi - msm: bam_dmux: Reduce debug logs to avoid watchdog bite
  *zeroblade1984 - msm8226:dtsi:Increase MSM Watchdog pet time
  *Taniya Das - msm: acpuclock-8226: Limit DDR to 200MHz for APSS frequency
  *Ke Liu - msm: acpuclock-8226: update corner mapping for 1.2 and 1.4 GHz speedbins
  *zeroblade1984 - cpufreq: Necessary updates to get ball rolling
  *zeroblade1984 - CPUFREQ: Few minor stuff
  *myfluxi - PM: devfreq: Fix simple_ondemand crashing on startup
  *zeroblade1984 - mpm-of:Partially revert previous changes
  *zeroblade1984 - Fix Vibration Control
  *zeroblade1984 - Fix Goodix panel drivers as well
  *zeroblade1984 - ft5x06:Fix notifier for suspend
  *tarun93 - dts: msm8226 msm_thermal use tsens_tz_sensor5 for thermal throttling instead of tsens_tz_sensor0 (EXPERIMENTAL)
  *Evisceration - msm: thermal: allow to configure poll interval from userspace
  *franciscofranco - msm: thermal: add Franco's cleaned up in-kernel driver
  *franciscofranco - msm: thermal: fix init with msm_thermal
  *Chris Fries - ARM: Use -mtune=cortex-a7 for 8226/8610
  *Pranav Vashi - msm: use of swp{b} is deprecated for ARMv6+
  *H. Peter Anvin - kernel: Replace timeconst.pl with a bc script
  *Dan Pasanen - timeconst.pl: fix perl warning
  *Riley Andrews - android: drivers: workaround debugfs race in binder
  *Ajay Dudani - Staging: android: binder: Add some tracepoints
  *Tejun Heo - workqueue: make all workqueues non-reentrant
  *Mike Snitzer - block: disable entropy contributions for nonrot devices
  *Jann Horn - fs: take i_mutex during prepare_binprm for set[ug]id executables
  *Kirill A. Shutemov - mm: Fix NULL pointer dereference in madvise(MADV_WILLNEED) support
  *Sasha Levin - vfs: read file_handle only once in handle_to_path
  *Rabin Vincent - tracing/syscalls: Ignore numbers outside NR_syscalls' range
  *Will Deacon - tracing/syscalls: Fix perf syscall tracing when syscall_nr == -1
  *fefifofum - armani: defconfig: Enable FIOPS IO scheduler
  *Shaohua Li - block: fiops ioscheduler core

Project name: android_bootable_recovery
  *Tao Bao - updater: Hoist fsync() to outer loop.
  *Jesse Zhao - Initialize stashbase even stash_max_blocks = 0
  *Sami Tolvanen - Support resuming block based OTAs
  *Elliott Hughes - Fix recovery image text rendering.
  *Matt Mower - recovery: Separate blkid.tab for vold in recovery
  *Steve Kondik - sr: Deep rainbow integration
  *Steve Kondik - updater: Add LZMA support to blockimg
  *James Sullins - improve Rainbow Mode
  *CEnnis91 - RAINBOW MODE MOTHERFUCKERS
  *Tom Marshall - recovery: bu: Support verity, incremental OTAs, and encrypted data
  *Tom Marshall - recovery: bu: disable xcomp during backup/restore
  *Michael Bestas - sr: Fix log text color

Project name: android_art
  *Jie Cheng - ART: Tuning compiler thread count for application runtime
  *Chirayu Desai - Improve dalvik cache pruning
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "Revert "AArch64: Fix incorrect use of preceding LIR.""
  *Chirayu Desai - Allow skipping of dalvik cache pruning if boot marker is in place.

Project name: android
  *Ethan Chen - manifest: Remove separate paths for 8610/8226 HALs
  *Myself5 - manifest: add CarbonWallpapers
  *weldoncyngn - adding android-support-test for espresso test
  *Arnav Gupta - manifest: move mips prebuilts into notdefault
  *Myself5 - You are not a CM repo
  *Myself5 - manifest: rewrite to be able to pick from CM gerrit
  *Abhisek Devkota - Fixup Freetype project & revision
  *Myself5 - update readme for lp5.1
  *Joey Hewitt - CVE Fix, track higher rev of conscrypt
  *PhaseBurn - Adding qcom sepolicy globally
  *Ryan N. Norris - Fix cmsdk repo path.
  *Patrick Campanale - Added our fork of cmsdk
  *Brint E. Kriebel - manifest: Update to freetype 2.6.0
  *Myself5 - Revert "Changed a few repos"
  *Patrick Campanale - Changed a few repos that we are resetting a few weeks back to fix some bugs
  *Myself5 - Fix Derp
  *Brandon McAnsh - cm: Use fork of aarch64 gcc for darwin as well
  *Steve Kondik - cm: Use fork of aarch64 gcc
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - 5.1.1_r3 -> 5.1.1_r6
  *José Adolfo Galdámez - manifest: remove final > extra
  *Adnan Begovic - Add cmsdk prebuilts repo.
  *Abhisek Devkota - Add Android Support Library prebuilts
  *STELIX - Manifest - Fix another stupid derp
  *Steve Kondik - Manifest - Switch to cm fork of external/lzma
  *Sean Hoyt - Remove device specfic exynos repo
  *STELIX - Manifest - Fix a stupid derp
  *STELIX - Manifest - track our own...
  *Myself5 - manifest: change the way to handle our repos
  *Michael Bestas - Manifest - Remove external/srec
  *STELIX - Manifest - use some our own telephony stuff

Project name: android_libcore
  *Christopher Ferris - Remove forced alignment code.
  *Roman Birg - libcore: add a way to clear cached time zone strings

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_MusicVisualization
  *Andreas Gampe - MusicVisualization: Force 32bit

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_Basic
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_HoloSpiral
  *Andreas Gampe - HoloSpiral: Force 32bit

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_Galaxy4
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Andreas Gampe - Galaxy4: Force 32bit
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_PhotoPhase
  *Abhisek Devkota - REAL_GET_TASKS > GET_TASKS
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_NoiseField
  *Andreas Gampe - NoiseField: Force 32bit

Project name: android_packages_wallpapers_PhaseBeam
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Andreas Gampe - PhaseBeam: Force 32bit
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_inputmethods_LatinIME
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Julien "_FrnchFrgg_" RIVAUD - Add support for Bépo keyboard layout
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_services_Mms
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_services_Telephony
  *Roman Birg - Network Settings: default user mode to preferred mode
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - Network Settings: don't crash on bad lookup
  *Roman Birg - Network settings: re-enable network preference selection
  *Chirayu Desai - For non-data SIMs, only set user configured mode, not preferred mode.
  *Chirayu Desai - Remove network mode handling for other SIM
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - Telephony : Null check cellInfo before calling addAll
  *LuK1337 - Telephony: Allow com.android.phone to use CMHW
  *Adnan Begovic - telephony: Don't bypass telephony stack when switching RAT.
  *Amit Mahajan - DO NOT MERGE Change to make STK related intents protected.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *jlask - Display the correct strings for network type summary
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *emancebo - telephony: fix APN msim issue where both sims show the same APNs
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Chirayu Desai - Rewrite network type summary handling
  *Danesh M - Telephony : Add support for config_hardcodeDefaultMobileNetworks
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *dankoman - [2/3] Telephony: Proximity speaker
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Lin Ma - Telephony: Add roaming mode options to mobile network settings
  *garwedgess - [4/5] Telephony: Breathing missedcall/sms/voicemail
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *mengsun - Fix phone not initialized exception
  *Danny Baumann - Style non-interactive dialog in the same way as interactive one.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Lin Ma - TeleService: pass sub ID to APN setting
  *AragaoAnderson - Telephony: Bye bye Holo USSD dialog
  *Andrew Lee - Restyle USSD AlertDialog.
  *Danny Baumann - Update activity title if called in MSIM case.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Kryten2k35 - Call recording encoder/format choice 2/3
  *Janson Kang - Fix National Roaming
  *lichti1901 - National Data Roaming [2/3]

Project name: android_packages_services_Telecomm
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Bruno Martins - Telecomm: Avoid NPE when invoking setAudioParameters
  *Steve Kondik - telecom: Move CMHW to CMSDK
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Bruno Martins - Telecomm: Make phone_type switch generic
  *Ethan Chen - Revert "Telecom: don't set incall state when call was disconnected"
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *ljzyal - Telecomm: Support Samsung Dual Sims Phone phone_type switch
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Chris Sarbora - Update to latest api level
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *LuK1337 - msim: Fix saving default sim from select SIM dialog (2/2)
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - Telecom : Add callInfo provider abstraction
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - Telecom : Remove null check for blacklist
  *Roman Birg - Telecom: don't set incall state when call was disconnected
  *garwedgess - [5/5] Telecomm: Breathing missedcall/sms/voicemailcemail
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Allow system apps to query the voicemail number.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Show multi-line notification if there's more than 1 missed call.

Project name: android_packages_apps_Settings
  *LorDClockaN - Settings: Toast icon switch (2/2)
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: remove contributors cloud margin/padding
  *Diogo Ferreira - Settings: Only show multi-sim card configuration for owners
  *James Hiew - Long press no longer copies to clipboard if there is nothing to copy
  *d34d - APN: Filter MVNOs by SPN, GID1 and IMSI
  *Myself5 - Revert "Settings - instant reboot action trigger (2/2)"
  *James Hiew - Get a handle for UserManager at creation
  *Roman Birg - Protected apps: fixup rotation states
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: fix fc for system apps with null applicationInfo
  *Adnan Begovic - Settings: Avoid possible NPE if resolve infos return null.
  *Lin Ma - Settings: Fix a crash caused by null pointer
  *Adnan Begovic - Settings: Utilize cyanogenmod.permission.MODIFY_PROFILES.
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: check bt pan service before use it
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: hide qs tiles with sensitive data
  *Myself5 - [1/2] Settings: Add Button to Recents to open App as Floating
  *lion0738 - [2/2] Settings: option to launch heads up in floating mode
  *rogersb11 - Gesture anywhere floating switch 2/2
  *Roman Birg - Settings: fix up advanced mode logic
  *Gabriele M - Settings: Always enable the per-app pulse light settings
  *stofstik - Added show volume to tile chooser
  *AdrianDC - LEDs Brightness [1/2]: Lights notifications brightness support
  *AdrianDC - Lights with Screen On [2/2]: Optional allowment of lights
  *Michael Bestas - Add back high SMS limits
  *Steve Kondik - settings: Animation scale seekbars
  *HazouPH - [2/2] Camera button support
  *Martin Brabham - Fix the improper string and increment database version to kick off a new indexing job.
  *maxwen - [1/2] SystemUI: Add time-context headers to notification header
  *Scott Mertz - Settings: obey prevent accidental wakeup default
  *Steve Kondik - settings: LiveDisplay color profiles
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - Settings: add a way to reset quick settings tiles
  *Steve Kondik - settings: Move CMHW to CMSDK
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: contributors cloud
  *Roman Birg - Settings: update time zone strings on date change
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Brandon McAnsh - Development: Add choices to 'Stay Awake' preference
  *Roman Birg - Settings: add a way to not localize zone selections
  *Matt Mower - Settings: Match pulse speed to frameworks default
  *Brandon McAnsh - Device info: Remove IMEI info from SIM status
  *emancebo - settings: add IMEI information to msim device status page
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - Settings: report stats upload immediately
  *PhaseBurn - Adding new devs, changing a couple existing around... and some string changes.
  *Patrick Campanale - Updated strings for About Carbon
  *Myself5 - Rework the DevCard Layout
  *Roman Birg - Settings: improved stats upload logic
  *Michael Bestas - Cleanup SoundSettings
  *Michael Bestas - Use correct icons for sound settings
  *d34d - Show "Lock screen & fingerprint" when supported
  *Dave Kover - Expose values for themes.
  *Adnan Begovic - Settings: Refactor to point at Profiles in CMSDK.
  *Myself5 - fix my Derp fixs Derp
  *Myself5 - Fix Derp about missing </string-array>
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Dave Kover - Update iconography to VectorDrawable and adjust coloring.
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - ApnSettings: Exclude MVNO listings that are known not to match
  *Myself5 - update me in about carbon
  *d34d - Include subQuality when returning from EncryptionInterstitial
  *Roman Birg - Settings: use new LockSettings
  *Roman Birg - Settings: continue factory reset if user leaves activity
  *Roman Birg - Settings: fix a few color picker inconsistentcies
  *d34d - Don't allow deleting last remaining fingerprint
  *Roman Birg - Settings: don't crash when dismissing FRP
  *Roman Birg - Settings: make FRP wipe dialog not cancelable
  *Ed Falk - Disable sim toggle switch if preference is disabled
  *Roman Birg - Settings: display light pulse dialog settings conditionally
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - Settings: Long Term Orbits (LTO)
  *Danesh M - Add data connection toggle for MSIM
  *d34d - Remove use of "firmly" from fingerprint strings
  *d34d - No purchase confirmations for fingerprints at this time
  *d34d - Check for null activity before calling getSetupBar
  *Danesh M - Revert "Settings : Add contributors word cloud"
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Don't include all resource densities
  *Erica Chang - Settings: Hide radio band selection based on config Ticket: RENDANG-355
  *Roman Birg - Settings: add fallback strings to device versioning for metrics
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Abhisek Devkota - Fix Battery % display in saver threshold
  *Roman Birg - Settings: add Kiev time zones to picker
  *Asher Simonds - Settings: Update profiles settings dashboard icon.
  *Adnan Begovic - Settings: Make sure we're getting the instance of ProfileManager.
  *d34d - Setup: Call setUseFingerprint() when enrollment finished
  *Roman Birg - Settings: fix reversed name/id fields in metrics
  *Dave Kover - Remove hardcoded textAppearance for better theme support.
  *APOPHIS9283 - Fix config_proximityCheckOnWake setting handling
  *Roman Birg - MasterClear: fix FRP wipe crash
  *STELIX - Slim : Stripped down performance profiles Settings from CM (Fix)
  *STELIX - Settings - NotifManager: some missing import class
  *Nicholas Flintham - Slim : Stripped down performance profiles Settings from CM
  *Nicholas Flintham - Add a 2 sec timeout for heads up notifications
  *Daniel Koman - Settings: "headsup" to "heads-up"
  *Jean-Pierre Rasquin - [1/2] SlimHeadsUp: Add a global 3-way switch
  *Lars Greiss - Settings: add headsup manifest permission
  *Lars Greiss - Settings: Slim heads up customizations for LP (2/2)
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - HeadsUp options [2/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - HeadsUp: add timeout option (2/2)"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - [Heads up Swipe] A more user friendly summary"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - [Heads up] Touch to hide (2/2)"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - Move Heads-Up settings to Notification Manager"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - QS: Add Headsup tile [2/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - Add Feature: Heads Up custom text/background color, transparency"
  *STELIX - Revert "[Settings] Improve HeadsUp [2/2]"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings: add HeadsUp button in status bar header (2/2)"
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings: HeadsUp snooze function [2/2]"
  *d34d - Keep screen on during fingerprint enrollment
  *Stephen Bird - Protected Apps: Monitor unlock status
  *Roman Birg - Settings: fix setting light FC
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Include "Fingerprint" in the unlock title
  *d34d - Fix aliasing in FingerprintProgressBar
  *d34d - Fix navigating fallback security via setup wizard
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Match Enrollment UI with SetupWizard
  *Steve Kondik - settings: Fix livedisplay settings
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Cancel timeout if user leaves enrollment
  *d34d - Use theme_accent for manage_fingerptins_primary_color
  *d34d - Remove manage fingerprints from enrollment setup
  *d34d - OOBE: Set next label when fingerprint enrollment done
  *d34d - Add LOCKSCREEN_BIOMETRIC_WEAK_FALLBACK to fallbackIntent
  *Michael Bestas - Remove unused xml
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Set untranslatable
  *d34d - Add fingerprint enrollment stats
  *d34d - Add SetupManageFingerprints to setup wizard flow
  *d34d - Cancel error timeout when enrollment finished
  *Roman Birg - Settings: hide light pulse settings if not available
  *Adnan Begovic - Settings: Point to classes within cmsdk.
  *d34d - Enroll fingerprint via SetupWizard [1/2]
  *d34d - Show error state when fingerprint read times out
  *d34d - Only show fingerprint for primary user
  *Andy Mast - Keyguard Fingerprint: Lock immediately when fp is used [2/2]
  *Roman Birg - Settings: update community metrics
  *d34d - Fingerprint: Fingerprint enrollment
  *Andy Mast - Fingerprint: Add summary text to 'manage fingerprints'
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - Performance: Add Path for Fast Charge"
  *Andy Mast - Add fingerprint permission [2/2]
  *cretin45 - Settings: Add config for not allowing calls/sms being set to > slot 1
  *Matt Garnes - Make preferred install location option configurable.
  *Brandon McAnsh - Settings: Remove Performance Settings
  *d34d - Fix patch derpage for fingerprint settings
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Wilhelm Fitzpatrick - Settings: use WhisperPush v2 if it is installed in place of v1
  *Andy Mast - Show dialog if max number of fingerprints has been reached
  *Andy Mast - Rename/Delete UI in fingerprint list
  *Andy Mast - Enable fingerprint option in Settings [3/3]
  *Roman Birg - Settings: add wifi ap dialog 'show password' default overlay
  *Christopher R. Palmer - settings: Fix developer options crash when mBackupManager is null
  *NBruderman - Settings: Make the Wifi regions translatable
  *STELIX - Settings - Super Slim PIE Fix [2/2]
  *eyosen - fix slim shortcuts fc
  *rogersb11 - Allow more slim action tile actions and add some
  *rogersb11 - Add Restart SystemUI to slim actions 1/2
  *Lars Greiss - Settings: SlimPie (2/2) - from BlissRom
  *Daniel Koman - Settings - Re-order strings and arrays
  *STELIX - Settings - Fix slim actions
  *STELIX - Settings - Ooops! :-O
  *Roman Birg - Settings: fix confirm pattern crash on rotate
  *Utkarsh Gupta - Remove stray file
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Andrew Dodd - wifi: Allow configuration of country code for wifi (3/3)
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: wifi priorities
  *Jorge Ruesga - settings: dynamic tiles
  *Hemanth kumar B - Avoid SElinux denial accessing SIM card lock
  *Raju Yadav - Avoid SElinux denial accessing IMEI information
  *Brandon McAnsh - SecuritySettings: Assert the instance of KeyStore before use
  *Roman Birg - Settings: persist profile dialogs while rotationg screen
  *cretin45 - Settings: Ensure fragment is visible before updating footer
  *Adnan Begovic - Settings: Disable mobile network settings if sub is invalid/unusable.
  *d34d - Don't clear cache on null UiDetailProvider
  *d34d - BatteryLight: Reset all settings back to default
  *STELIX - Revert "Settings - Navigation Bar Customization [2/2]"
  *Stephen Bird - Settings: option to disable torch when the screen turns off: Fix 2
  *Roman Birg - Settings - Enable Developer options by default
  *tobitege - Settings - Fix default battery text color (1/2)
  *STELIX - Add Europe/Rome
  *Elliott Hughes - Add Europe/Madrid.
  *Samuel Asteberg - Add Europe/Istanbul timezone
  *Elliott Hughes - Add Pacific/Noumea.
  *STELIX - Settings: option to disable torch when the screen turns off: Fix
  *tobitege - Add Europe/Berlin
  *Daniel Koman - Settings: vector support for action icons
  *fusionjack - DSLV: Resize system icons to match vector drawable size
  *Altaf-Mahdi - Settings: Double tap to sleep anywhere on the lock screen (2/2)
  *Janson Kang - Task Manager: No longer requires SystemUI restart
  *Alex Cruz - Settings - CAF Task Manager switch [2/2]
  *Altaf-Mahdi - Settings: option to disable torch when the screen turns off (2/2)
  *STELIX - Settings - Custom scrolling values: Change SeekBar
  *Bajee11 - [3/5] Settings: Breathing missedcall/sms/voicemail
  *AdrianDC - Settings: Fix HighTouchSensitivity & TouchscreenHovering
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - MasterClear: update UI
  *Janson Kang - Settings: Option to enable/disable scrolling cache
  *scott - Settings - custom scrolling values [1/2]
  *Stephen Bird - Protected Apps: Fix rotate FC
  *Danny Baumann - Use framework name and icon for system UID.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - Settings: fix potential NPE
  *yong.zou - Settings: Fix there is no sounds and delays 1s when pressing "Touch sounds" sometimes
  *Gianmarco Reverberi - PrivacyGuard: restore ListView position on resume, for real
  *Jinpyo-laptop - Over scroll effects [2/2]
  *Lokesh Chamane - Settings: HeadsUp snooze function [2/2]
  *Shaun Eaton - Settings - Update Slim Actions
  *Altaf-Mahdi - Settings: add HeadsUp button in status bar header (2/2)
  *BigBrother1984 - [Settings] Improve HeadsUp [2/2]
  *tobitege - Avoid adding empty entries in list
  *tobitege - Fix carrier label switch
  *tobitege - DSLV: fix NPE in ActionListViewSettings with mActionConfigs
  *Danny Baumann - Fix up increasing ring tone volume preview behaviour.
  *Dan Pasanen - Settings: remove mobile networks menu if ro.radio.noril is set
  *longyu.huang - the status of brightness not refresh in power control widget after manual adjustment of brightnes
  *yong.zou - Settings: Fix preferred install location dialog will dismiss after rotating screen
  *Brandon McAnsh - Profiles: Get Default profile with its UUID instead of name
  *yong.zou - Settings: Fix setting app install location as "Removable SD card" without SD card inserted
  *STELIX - Settings - Strings CleanUp
  *Danny Baumann - Integrate mobile network settings into SIM settings for MSIM.
  *tobitege - Fix custom date format entry and european styles
  *Shareef Ali - Settings: fix an issue where text is not showing up on first instance.
  *Michael Bestas - Cleanup SMS limits
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *longping.zou - Settings:Not responding In-app search function
  *Jorge Ruesga - profiles: respect lockscreen policies
  *Pavel Zhamaitsiak - Add button in "hidden" settings to flip "VoLTE Provisioned" flag
  *Raj Yengisetty - Profiles: fix SeekBarVolumizer behavior
  *Roman Birg - Settings: use WindowManager to set custom DPI
  *STELIX - Settings - QS: NavBar Tile - redirect long-click
  *tobitege - Fix NPE in slimshortcuts if no Icon is found
  *Jubakuba - Settings: Slim Actions to Shortcuts
  *tobitege - Settings - Add European-style date formats
  *Kra1o5 - Settings - Add option to set default custom function to button recents (2/2)
  *Ateek Ujjawal - Fix Network Traffic VS tab crash on msim devices
  *Myself5 - Readd KK Carbon Easteregg
  *Myself5 - Revert "Add our old Carbon KK EasterEgg"
  *Myself5 - Add our old Carbon KK EasterEgg
  *AlmightyMegadeth00 - Settings - Navigation Bar Customization [2/2]

Project name: android_packages_apps_ThemeChooser
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Andreas - Show an AlertDialog when clicking Get More
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Dave Kover - Update iconography.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *dhacker29 - Add CleanSpec.mk to fix the build errors after UI update
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Small UI refresh
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_PhoneCommon
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Rohit Yengisetty - AnimUtils : clear listeners when animation completes or is terminated
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Rohit Yengisetty - PhoneCommon : Add layouts to support hdpi devices

Project name: android_packages_apps_Email
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Allow saving attachments even if there's no intent handling them.
  *Danny Baumann - Allow download of compressed attachments.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Don't cancel PendingIntents used for AlarmManager.
  *Danny Baumann - Optimize connection loss and re-gain behaviour.
  *Danny Baumann - Refine thread handling.
  *Danny Baumann - Properly unregister alarm manager callbacks.
  *Danny Baumann - Use AlarmManager to schedule an IDLE connection restart.
  *Danny Baumann - Don't auto-register IDLE when gaining connection.
  *Danny Baumann - Do less work on IDLE refresh.
  *Danny Baumann - Improve debug logging.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Use an inexact timer for the IDLE refresh.
  *Danny Baumann - Don't throw a NPE when operating on a destroyed list.
  *Danny Baumann - Fix some more argument order issues.
  *Danny Baumann - Simplify logic.
  *Danny Baumann - Fix some typos.
  *Danny Baumann - Don't solely rely on the presence of RECENT for checking for new mail.
  *Danny Baumann - Don't re-sync when refreshing the IDLE connection.
  *Danny Baumann - Fix crash when attempting to view EML files.
  *Danny Baumann - Reset idling flag when cancelling early due to being cancelled.
  *Danny Baumann - Add some debug statements.
  *Danny Baumann - Assign debug tags to IMAP communication output.
  *Danny Baumann - Fix argument order.
  *Danny Baumann - Simplify code.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - email: catch the correct exception while closing the buffers
  *Danny Baumann - Fix ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException.
  *Jorge Ruesga - email: fix NPE
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Scott Mertz - EmailTests: fix api change
  *Jorge Ruesga - email: fix tests

Project name: android_packages_apps_PackageInstaller
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *emancebo - PackageInstaller: add hook to manage packages via PRE_BOOT_COMPLETED event

Project name: android_packages_apps_BluetoothExt
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_ContactsCommon
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *emancebo - LookupProvider updates
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Rohit Yengisetty - SelectAccountActivity : Support local phone account
  *chengzhi.hou - Fix:Shouln't display any contacts after clean all letters in dialer search view.
  *cretin45 - ContactsCommon: Telephony expects sim_index
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Marcos Marado - string validation: check if the string is empty
  *Stephen Bird - EmergencyContacts: Check if quickdial number is an emergency number
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - ContactsCommon : Add createStarredPhoneOnlyLoader
  *Rohit Yengisetty - PhoneNumberLookup : have the mk file hold its absolute path for easy inclusion
  *Rohit Yengisetty - Add generic hooks for contact info lookup based on phone number
  *Rohit Yengisetty - ContactPhotoManager - Add ability to fetch contact bitmap based on photo id
  *Rohit Yengisetty - CheckableFlipDrawable : Add getter for front drawable
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Matt Garnes - Add local phone account as a writable AccountTypes.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_CMFileManager
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Fix bookmark string
  *Richard MacGregor - Regex metacharacters result in error post search
  *Stephen Bird - Search: Fix race condition with results display
  *Roman Birg - CMFM: don't apply search filter when search hasn't started
  *Roman Birg - CMFM: fix search mime type filter not applying
  *Stephen Bird - Bookmarks: check to see if a bookmark exists before adding it
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Richard MacGregor - FileManager: Fix shortcuts
  *Stephen Bird - Fix MediaScan issue w/ Deleting
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *herriojr - Fixed MediaScan Issue w/ Directories
  *herriojr - Fix Navigation back from Search
  *Stephen Bird - Refresh: stop refreshes in action
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *LuK1337 - NavigationActivity: Do not reload screen on rotation
  *kai.cao - Fix FileSystemInfo's ImageView shows incorrect picture in BreadcrumbView .
  *Matt Garnes - Fix improper exception handling during copy operation.
  *Roman Birg - CMFM: improved search performance
  *Matt Garnes - Improve copy/move performance with nio and reintroduce cancel.
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - RTL: move buttons to proper spot in nav drawer
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *kai.cao - Fix don't pop up "Actions" menu when long pressing on a file/folder after open and close "Use swipe gesture".
  *herriojr - Fixed ANR & Memory Leak Associated with 3GP
  *herriojr - Fixed search to actually open the clicked folder
  *herriojr - Fixed ANR associated with SecureStorage
  *herriojr - Revert "Made NavigationView reliant on FileObserver to keep up to date."
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *herriojr - Made NavigationView reliant on FileObserver to keep up to date.
  *kai.cao - [CMFileManager] Fix can't copy after disconnect with pc.
  *herriojr - ANR Caused by passes over Data Set on notifyDataSetChanged()
  *Stephen Bird - Secure Move: Check to make sure libtruecrypt correctly errored
  *herriojr - Fix Secure SD Card Entry to open folder.
  *herriojr - Refactored the ImageLoader a bit, so that it doesn't have trouble loading images.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *herriojr - Moved the sort of the data set off the UI Thread.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Dave Kover - Update launcher iconography.
  *herriojr - Changed NavigationView.refresh() in onResume() of the activity to try to restore the original position.
  *Stephen Bird - Preferences: Move huge paragraph description to own item
  *Stephen Bird - ProgressDialog: Require user to explicitly use the cancel button.
  *Stephen Bird - Editor: Handle content uri's in the editor
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - configurationChanged: Don't handle the orientation change in our main Activity
  *Stephen Bird - Secure Storage: Fix unlock button
  *Stephen Bird - Easy Mode: Fix exit on easy mode screen
  *weldoncyngn - Android.mk don't build source components in tests/
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - ActionBar TextSelection: Prevent overlay of textfield
  *Roman Birg - Shell console: fix bug in shell output stream
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - Fix parsing of shell command output regardless of encoding
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Properly validate fields when resetting password
  *Stephen Bird - onResume: Refresh current view
  *Stephen Bird - Sizes: Let disk usage show sizes as doubles
  *Stephen Bird - MediaScanning: Update with calls to Mediascanner
  *d34d - Delete destination file when copy fails
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Exchange
  *Danny Baumann - Fix authentication error notification click handling.

Project name: android_packages_apps_SoundRecorder
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Ed Falk - SoundRecorder: Add support for 1-channel WAV files
  *Adnan Begovic - SoundRecorder: Mark recorder as processed if we've saved the sample.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: OTAUpdates
  *Kryten2k35 - Added Waffle.io data and issue tracking
  *Kryten2k35 - Version 2.5.3
  *Kryten2k35 - Trim whitespace in the URL, just in case the developers add it in (they shouldn't)
  *Kryten2k35 - Fixed the ORS generation for the installafterflash files.
  *Kryten2k35 - Addons error:
  *Kryten2k35 - Enable debugging without having to use a device that is running a compatible ROM
  *Kryten2k35 - Verion 2.5.2
  *Kryten2k35 - Download location fix
  *Kryten2k35 - Merge mistake
  *Kryten2k35 - Changelog update 20150629
  *Kryten2k35 - Version bump to v2.5.1
  *Kryten2k35 - Fix for if theme isn't used in the build.prop
  *Kryten2k35 - Fix for if theme isn't used in the build.prop
  *Kryten2k35 - Added storage location in preferences
  *Kryten2k35 - Addons: Fixing much fo the recent problems with the addons
  *Kryten2k35 - Adds "Pro/Donate" preference to the settings menu
  *Kryten2k35 - ORS: Fix the generation of the OpenRecoveryScript
  *Kryten2k35 - Updated Addons seciton of the manual instructions
  *Kryten2k35 - Use version name rather than filename for update available text
  *Kryten2k35 - Fix IllegalStateExeption when downloading on some devices (hopefully)
  *Kryten2k35 - Missed out this"About page" button for pre-LP devices.
  *Kryten2k35 - Allow the AvailableActivity page to show the full version name without stripping spaces
  *Kryten2k35 - Enabled developers to set the default theme for the app
  *Kryten2k35 - Added Download location choosing by developers
  *Kryten2k35 - Added build prop Constants
  *Kryten2k35 - Fixed my own donation links always going to coinbase!
  *Kryten2k35 - Parse the download link's host and display it in AvailableActivity.
  *Kryten2k35 - Fixed using HTTP links instead of direct links. Now open properly if needed.
  *Kryten2k35 - Some more ad code
  *Kryten2k35 - Last few bits of the google services
  *Kryten2k35 - Ads: Cleaning up the last remnants of the ads
  *Kryten2k35 - Updated READMEs
  *Kryten2k35 - Android.mk: No longer require Google Play Services for AOSP building
  *Kryten2k35 - Cleaning up the master branch
  *Kryten2k35 - Catch BadTokenException
  *Kryten2k35 - Changelog alteration
  *Kryten2k35 - Left debugging on by mistake!
  *Kryten2k35 - Added some unnecessary files to gitignore
  *Kryten2k35 - Removed unnecessary files for AOSP building
  *Kryten2k35 - About moved to preferences
  *Kryten2k35 - Made Constants easier to read.
  *Kryten2k35 - Version bump
  *Kryten2k35 - Global varible strings for themes too
  *Kryten2k35 - Mobile Network detection global variable created
  *Kryten2k35 - Cleaned up storage location handling
  *Kryten2k35 - ORS information moved above the settings
  *Kryten2k35 - Fixed download location from the download manager
  *Kryten2k35 - Utils: Remove unused code
  *Kryten2k35 - Added method for determining external path
  *Kryten2k35 - ORS Script: Fixed InstallAfterFlash location
  *Kryten2k35 - Version bump to 2.4.4
  *Kryten2k35 - More NPE fixes
  *Kryten2k35 - NPE in AppReceiver
  *Kryten2k35 - Fix BitCoin ALWAYS showing for the developer donation options
  *Kryten2k35 - Update changelog
  *Kryten2k35 - Version 2.4.3
  *Kryten2k35 - Version bump 2.4.2
  *Kryten2k35 - Fix ORS generation failing on the download dir
  *Kryten2k35 - Remove add category on AOSP

Project name: android_packages_apps_Gallery2
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *cretin45 - Gallery2: Intents for image/video directory viewing/picking
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - Photo Gallery widget: fix NPE in getViewAt
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *root - Gallery2: Fix crash when Bluetooth service is disabled
  *Scott Warner - Add Storage preference (2/2)

Project name: android_packages_apps_Camera2
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *NBruderman - Camera2: Fix Undo button behaviour
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Fix storage location NPE
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *dcalandria - Add Storage preference (1/2)

Project name: android_packages_apps_Nfc
  *Jorge Ruesga - nfc: create a bootstrap service
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Mms-caf
  *Adnan Begovic - Mms: Don't try to send an SMS to a null destination.
  *Susheel nyamala - Fix mms failures due to invalid mmsc url
  *Roman Birg - Mms: show default app icon for unresolved links
  *Abhisek Devkota - REAL_GET_TASKS > GET_TASKS
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Richard MacGregor - Fix "To" label hide/show when adding/removing subject
  *Stephen Bird - MMS: Change subject logic
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Improve QuickMessage string
  *Ethan Chen - Mms: Check whether data is enabled on current subscription
  *Ethan Chen - Mms: Use system API for setDataEnabled
  *Stephen Bird - QuickMessage: Make useful on lockscreen
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Martin Brabham - Fix keyboard hiding and scrolling
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - Mms: fix keyboard hiding
  *Abhisek Devkota - Unbreak Mms
  *Brandon McAnsh - Mms: Close keyboard if scrolling in conversation history
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Abhisek Devkota - Temp Fix: Localize Smilies in Russian
  *Danesh M - Mms : Replace  REQUEST_CODE_PICK with REQUEST_CODE_ADD_RECIPIENTS
  *Danesh M - Revert "Drafts: Prevent duplicate drafts from being added"
  *Danesh M - Revert "Drafts: Fix instance where body of the message is lost."
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Drafts: Fix instance where body of the message is lost.
  *d34d - Delete vcard mms on error
  *Stephen Bird - Add Subject: Fix subject crash
  *Stephen Bird - ComposeMessage: Improve performance with large groups
  *herriojr - Fixed KeyGuard not being disabled on second quickmessage
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - Mms :  Don't load slideshow details for draft
  *Shlomy Reinstein - Fix detection of RTL language in 'from' field
  *Danesh Mondegarian - Calendar Attachment: decode URI for file name
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - Mms : Ensure text mode supports multiple content-types
  *Stephen Bird - Drafts: Prevent duplicate drafts from being added
  *Stephen Bird - Compose:  Hiding the "To" label when editing the subject
  *Rohit Yengisetty - Show Calendar Event attachment only if an activity can respond to the intent
  *Brandon McAnsh - QuickMessage: Add shortMessage to inputType
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Quick Message: Fix dual sim picker
  *razorloves - Enable heads-up style notifications on Mms app
  *Stephen Bird - Contact vCard: Dont crash if contact that is sent
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Nicholas Chum - Expose message link text color
  *Bajee11 - Mms: Breathing missedcall/sms/voicemail
  *Nicholas Chum - Expose message link text color
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Don't filter share intent
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Compose Message: Fix visual glitch.
  *Sultanxda - Add UAProf URL to carrier-specific configs
  *Danny Baumann - Create the contact photo manager as service.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Carrier-specific MMS limits
  *Danesh Mondegarian - Mms : Add users permission to prevent crash

Project name: android_packages_apps_Eleven
  *Abhisek Devkota - REAL_GET_TASKS > GET_TASKS
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Linus Lee - Eleven: Visualizer: Add back landscape mode
  *Linus Lee - Add ability to seek through track with circular motion
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Utkarsh Gupta - Visualizer tweaks
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Utkarsh Gupta - Upgrade visualizer
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Jorge Ruesga - eleven: fix invalid srt formats
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Utkarsh Gupta - Dynamically generate visualizer color
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Martin Brabham - AudioPreviewActivity: Better external audio previewing
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Linus Lee - Eleven: Add playlist cover art to search results
  *Linus Lee - Eleven: remove an unnecessary check when playing music to improve perf
  *Linus Lee - Eleven: Add a play Album option on songs
  *Linus Lee - Eleven: Remove inset from top tracks circle

Project name: android_packages_apps_InCallUI
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - InCallUI: Unbreak heads-up disabled incoming call.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *dankoman - [3/3] InCallUI: Proximity speaker
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Show waiting state in call title also for MSIM.
  *Adnan Begovic - InCallUi: Mitigate redial/recent call double tap state loss.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - [1/2] InCallUI: SmartMute
  *Chengzhi.Hou - Fix: The EndCallButton overlaps the digital key 0 after switch system language during an active call
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *tobitege - Fix proximity sensor with proximity wake option

Project name: android_packages_apps_Dialer
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *LuK1337 - Fix Dialer FC on guest user with phone calls allowed
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *jrizzoli - dialer: better smart call string
  *Danny Baumann - Ensure the smart dial name matcher is initialized in onStart().
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Fix up call log search UX.
  *Danny Baumann - Improve performance of call log.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *BadDaemon - Improve SmartDialer
  *Kryten2k35 - Enable Call Recording for the United Kingdom
  *Danny Baumann - Remove some dead code.
  *linuxxxxx - [2/2] Dialer: SmartMute
  *Danesh M - Dialer: Ensure device ids not null
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Update blacklist strings
  *Kryten2k35 - Call recording encoder/format choice 1/3
  *BlackDragon - Enable Call recording.

Project name: android_packages_apps_CellBroadcastReceiver
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Remove per-SIM CB configuration.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Calculator
  *Yvonne Wong - Calculator: fix localization for the widget
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - Calculator: do not allow multiple decimal points in a number
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Floating Calculator: Fix Hidden row of buttons
  *Stephen Bird - Cursor: Keep visible for long numbers
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Dave Kover - Remove duplicate color.
  *Raj Yengisetty - Calculator: allow for deletion when selector is next to a separator
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Floating Calculator: Reposition to fit landscape devices
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Calculator: Fix issue with overflowing text

Project name: android_packages_apps_AudioFX
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Nicholas Chum - Expose text color and background colors for Theming
  *Nicholas Chum - Expose actionbar background for Theming

Project name: android_packages_apps_Contacts
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Elike24 - Contacts: Fixed "%s" appearing in contact options in some languages
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Matt Garnes - Fix local account name display for groups.
  *Rohit Yengisetty - Contacts : Change 'up' actionbar indicator to a check mark in add/edit contacts
  *Martin Brabham - Remove arbitrary set visibility call
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Matt Garnes - Keep a local instance of mContactData when copying to SIM card.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *naman14 - Contacts:remove memory status from overflow in search mode
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Bluetooth
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Roman Birg - Bluetooth: request audio focus on incoming call
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Profiles
  *Roman Birg - ProfileTrustAgent: remove onStart override
  *Roman Birg - Profiles Trust: respect DPM; use new LockSettings
  *Adnan Begovic - Profiles: Refactor to point at Profiles in CMSDK.

Project name: android_packages_apps_CMUpdater
  *Jorge Ruesga - cmupdater: dont assume actionbar is present
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Brandon McAnsh - CMUpdater: Improve Android Wear notifications
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_TvSettings
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_CMWallpapers
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Terminal
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Calendar
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - prepareForSave: Dont set time in allday events
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - Calendar: when sharing calendar events use File.createTempFile
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Trebuchet
  *emancebo - Trebuchet: fix potential NPE when info is null
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Support STK app rename on MSIM
  *Pragnya Paramita - Trebuchet: STK app rename customization for latam region.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Richard MacGregor - Reset default view camera distance
  *Richard MacGregor - Fix wallpaperpreview for default wallpaper
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Linus Lee - Trebuchet: Make focus animate and move faster
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - Do not collapse Settings panel when reseting overview mode
  *Matt Garnes - Update default workspace to reference latest browser.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Show apps as unavailable when on unmounted storage
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Stephen Bird - Trebuchet: fix voice button proxy
  *Raj Yengisetty - Loader: use INVALID_RESTORE_PAGE to avoid unnecessarily synchronizing
  *d34d - Wallpaper: Allow multiple partners to be loaded
  *Brandon McAnsh - Launcher: Close OverviewMode when transitioning back to Workspace.State.NORMAL
  *Brandon McAnsh - Launcher: Close open folder when transitioning back to Workspace.State.NORMAL
  *Hayden Schoen - Folder Layout Revision
  *Stephen Bird - Protected Folders: Prevent the folder name from covering the toggle
  *Raj Yengisetty - Fade Adjacent Screens: disable this feature for App Drawer (paged)
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - Transition Effects: stack transition effect
  *Raj Yengisetty - FocusHelper: handle NPE with when getting workspace child
  *Roman Birg - Trebuchet: display search widget search box if available
  *Stephen Bird - Badge: Check count on bind
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Matt Garnes - Update default workspace configuration.
  *Matt Garnes - Hide workspace shortcuts during binding when AllApps is shown.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Matt Garnes - Fix unintended dynamic grid resize side effects.
  *Raj Yengisetty - Trebuchet: Fix popupMenu behavior and clean up old code.
  *d34d - Don't load title from intent if title loaded from DB
  *Stephen Bird - Scrolling: Fix fade in workspaces from ignoring us
  *Elektroschmock - Trebuchet: FloatMath is deprecated in API22
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - Trebuchet: Fix bug with removing items from folders
  *Steve Kondik - trebuchet: Externalize backup API key string
  *Stephen Bird - Rotation: fix icons disappearing
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Martin Brabham - Stop unnecessary exception posting to logcat.
  *Stephen Bird - RTL: fix app drawer layout
  *Brandon McAnsh - Launcher: Check if componentName is null prior to getPackageName()
  *Matt Garnes - Update default workspace.
  *Stephen Bird - Move icons to fit within Dynamic grid upon resize.
  *Roman Birg - Trebuchet: send metrics values as strings
  *Linus Lee - Fix power save mode broken ui/animations
  *Linus Lee - Trebuchet: fix excessive drawing with folders
  *Sam Mortimer - Move tablet preference ahead of the default
  *Steve Kondik - trebuchet: Don't use new hotness on tablets
  *Steve Kondik - trebuchet: Enable the new hotness by default.
  *Martin Brabham - Trebuchet Statistics:  - Add plumbing for sending events.  - Add aggregation service that runs on some interval  - Hook send events into respective UX interactions
  *xuke.yin - Fix the hint text of rename folder can't change with system language
  *Raj Yengisetty - Trebuchet: fix NPE during touch events

Project name: android_packages_apps_UnifiedEmail
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Marcos Marado - Don't assume that a string isn't empty
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danny Baumann - Remove obsolete theme.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_LockClock
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Zach Prezkuta - Allow user to change background color/transparency for the widget, for greater compatibility with various wallpapers
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Brandon McAnsh - LockClock: Only show timestamp if it can fit
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_Browser
  *Mrcl1450 - Browser: add duckduckgo search engine to DE locale

Project name: android_packages_apps_Stk
  *Abhisek Devkota - REAL_GET_TASKS > GET_TASKS
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Indicate which sub-activity the app name broadcast applies to
  *Paramananda Pradhan - Add intent to send STK app name
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Amit Mahajan - DO NOT MERGE Change to add STK_PERMISSION for stk related commands.
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Amit Mahajan - DO NOT MERGE Change to add STK_PERMISSION for stk related commands.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Chirayu Desai - Fix the SIM1 launcher
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - Revert "STK: use single icon as per latest AOSP 5.1"
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_apps_DeskClock
  *Adnan Begovic - DeskClock: Externalize permissions to CMSDK.
  *Adnan Begovic - DeskClock: Utilize cyanogenmod.permission.MODIFY_PROFILES.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Dave Kover - Expose FAB elevation value for themes.
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Improve & fix alarm permission strings
  *Matt Garnes - Allow alarms to be modified by 3rd parties.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Yadrishnikov Yaroslav - Allow theming numpad
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Fix rescheduling of alarms that are snoozed
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Adnan Begovic - DeskClock: Refactor to point at Profiles in CMSDK.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Raj Yengisetty - DeskClock: fix behavior with alarms when device is off
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Annie Chin - DeskClock: Correctly reschedule alarms on system time change
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_providers_DownloadProvider
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh Mondegarian - DownloadManager : Only remove stale id if download is not deleted
  *Roman Birg - DownloadManager: allow ACCESS_ALL_DOWNLOADS to be granted via whitelist
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import

Project name: android_packages_providers_ContactsProvider
  *Raj Yengisetty - Add URI matcher entry for CONTACTS_GROUP
  *Rohit Yengisetty - ContactsProvider : Retain SIM account during account clean up

Project name: android_packages_providers_MediaProvider
  *Maunik Shah - Screenshots info is not updated when device is plugged in MTP mode
  *Michael Bestas - Fix mounting of non-FAT formatted SD cards (2/2)

Project name: android_packages_providers_TelephonyProvider
  *Roman Birg - TelephonyProvider: change default user nw mode to invalid
  *Danesh M - Revert "MmsProvider : Add ability to get thread information in search"
  *Chirayu Desai - Add the user set network mode to the siminfo table
  *Martin Brabham - [MMS-55]: Add new column when creating a new database and table or upgrade existing table.
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Danesh M - MmsProvider : Add ability to get thread information in search
  *Rohit Yengisetty - TelephonyProvider : Add sub_id to ICC columns

Project name: android_packages_providers_ThemesProvider
  *d34d - Specify locale when using String.format()
  *Tom Powell - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Properly account for lock wallpaper previews
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *d34d - Avoid OOME when generating many wallpaper previews
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Michael Bestas - Automatic translation import
  *Richard MacGregor - Delete preview table rows on theme update
  *Richard MacGregor - Handle null parameters when creating query strings

Project name: android_bionic
  *Men_in_black007 - cortex-a53: Use cortex-a7/bionic/memset.S instead of cortex-a15/bionic/memset.S
  *Christopher Ferris - Remove pushes from memsets (krait/cortex-a9).
  *Christopher Ferris - Replace bx lr with update of pc from the stack.
  *Chih-Hung Hsieh - Use unified syntax to compile with both llvm and gcc.
  *Christopher Ferris - Add optimized cortex-a7/cortex-a53 memset/memcpy.
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "Replace memcpy with the cortex-strings implementation"
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "Add optimized cortex-a7/cortex-a53 memset/memcpy."
  *Jake Weinstein - libc: remove bcopy from memmove on 64-bit architectures
  *Elliott Hughes - Fix lgamma_r/lgammaf_r/lgammal_r for -0.
  *Kyle Repinski - libc: Fix strict-aliasing violations.
  *LuK1337 - cortex-a7: Fix build
  *LuK1337 - cortex-a7: set proper memcmp.S path
  *Christopher Ferris - Add optimized cortex-a7/cortex-a53 memset/memcpy.
  *Steve Kondik - libm: Fix makefiles
  *Amaury Le Leyzour - Add aarch64 instructions wherever possible
  *Shu Zhang - libm: arm: Add arm specific floor() optimization
  *Elliott Hughes - Fix our <complex.h> support.
  *Elliott Hughes - Get new coshl, sinhl, and tanhl implementations from upstream.
  *Elliott Hughes - Sync libm with upstream.
  *Varun Chitre - libc : memcpy : allow to disable opt for some targets

Project name: android_device_xiaomi_armani
  *tarun93 - Custom Tweaks, Script & Clean(WARNING!!NOOB COMMIT PLS IGNORE THIS COMMIT xD)
  *tarun93 - init.armani.rc : permission fix
  *tarun93 - thermal:loosen thermals a bit
  *kairi_zeroblade - Switch to per-core swapping
  *Kra1o5 - Revert "Add overlay for non-roaming operator"
  *fefifofum - Update fingerprint from latest official release
  *fefifofum - Show app install location option
  *fefifofum - Update fingerprint from latest official release
  *Kra1o5 - Add overlay for non-roaming operator
  *fefifofum - Use prebuilt libOmxVdecHevc
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - media: Switch to lower-end codecs
  *tarun93 - Adapt to carbon 5.1
  *fefifofum - overlay: Enable proximity check on screen wake
  *fefifofum - Enable FIOPS IO scheduler by default
  *fefifofum - sepolicy: Address mediaserver denial
  *fefifofum - Nothing to see here
  *fefifofum - Remove unused mms overlay
  *fefifofum - Set fingerprint and other device props
  *fefifofum - Enable drm prop
  *fefifofum - Don't symlink firmware files
  *fefifofum - Reorganize makefiles
  *fefifofum - sepolicy: Address wcnss_service denial
  *fefifofum - Don't need to copy FFMPEG config anymore
  *fefifofum - overlay: Mms: Show smsc and configure enter key
  *fefifofum - sepolicy: Address bootanim denial

Project name: android_device_qcom_common
  *Steve Kondik - power: Boost improvements
  *Steve Kondik - power: Update boost parameters
  *Steve Kondik - power: Updates for msm8916/msm8939
  *Marcos Marado - Adding init for msm8909
  *Dilip Gudlur - power: Enable 4+0 core config for display off cases
  *Steve Kondik - power: Use default video encode/decode hints on 8916
  *Marcos Marado - Guard variable expansion: string between quotes
  *Steve Kondik - power: More tunings
  *Steve Kondik - power: Additional changes for 8994
  *Steve Kondik - power: Send 8994 perf commands ourselves
  *Steve Kondik - power: Add features to the 8994 PowerHAL
  *Chirayu Desai - power-8916: Enable the perf options for performance mode

Project name: android_device_qcom_sepolicy
  *Howard M. Harte - sepolicy: perfd to have access to mediaserver
  *Stephen Boyd - sepolicy: Add thermal and irqbalancer sockets
  *Tatenda Chipeperekwa - sepolicy: Add policy for SurfaceFlinger access to rotator device
  *Arun Kumar K.R - SEAndroid: Allow SurfaceFlinger to access dynamic_fps node
  *Sungjun Park - Bluetooth: Update Bluetooth security rules
  *Krishna Chaitanya Parimi - sepolicy: allow mm-pp-daemon to set debug property
  *Krishna Chaitanya Parimi - sepolicy: allow mm-pp-daemon to have access to sysfs_graphics
  *Krishna Chaitanya Parimi - sepolicy: allow mm-pp-daemon to use binders in user variant
  *Sravan Kumar D.V.N - sepolicy: Add SELinux policy rule for pp daemon socket calls
  *Nitesh Gupta - sepolicy: Add sepolicy rules for display clients
  *Nitesh Gupta - sepolicy: Add context label for '/persist/display/*'
  *Alexy Joseph - Seandroid: Add policy for dts configurator and notifier nodes
  *Dinesh K Garg - sepolicy: add permissions to set system property
  *Susheel Yadagiri - sepolicy: add rule to support tcm write on dpmwrapper socket
  *Susheel Yadagiri - sepolicy: allow dpmd to create self socket and netlink socket.
  *Susheel Yadagiri - sepolicy: allow dpmd to connect to system_server
  *Susheel Yadagiri - sepolicy: Allow iptable rule addition when WQE is enabled
  *Sanket Khidkikar - cnd: Allow nims to be removed
  *Boxiang Pan - Sepolicy: add rule to support ATP feature
  *Steve Kondik - sepolicy: Allow time_daemon to use POSIX clocks
  *dcashman - Label factory reset protection partition.
  *Ameya Thakur - selinux: Peripheral manager: Allow system server to talk to per_mgr
  *Ameya Thakur - sepolicy: Update policy for peripheral manager
  *Krishna Konda - sepolicy: Update sepolicy for qseecom rpmb component
  *Ameya Thakur - sepolicy: Add support for pm-proxy executable
  *Naseer Ahmed - sepolicy: Allow write to S3D node
  *Tatenda Chipeperekwa - SEAndroid: Add access to res_info sysfs node
  *Avijit Kanti Das - Seandroid: Add policy for energy-awareness.
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - common: Fixup healthd's ability to deal with poweroff alarms
  *Manu Prasad - WFD: Revert SELinux changes for wfd running in its own service/domain
  *Mukund Mittal - sepolicy:Allow mm-qcamerad to access sensormanager service access.
  *Shiju Mathew - sepolicy: Update BCL sysfs nodes in file context

Project name: android_build
  *Łukasz Domeradzki - JustArchi's ArchiDroid Optimizations V4.1
  *Tao Bao - releasetools: Fix the bug when deleting files.
  *Tao Bao - releasetools: Fix the bug in symlink deletion.
  *luca020400 - build: allow using host flex binary
  *Anthony King - build: Allow QC platforms to share/customize HAL variants
  *Ethan Chen - Revert "msm8909 uses the same branches as msm8916"
  *Marcos Marado - msm8909 uses the same branches as msm8916
  *Tom Powell - repopick: open changes are either NEW or OPEN, not just OPEN
  *Tom Powell - Fix custom URL error. Merged from cm_build_config
  *Anthony King - repopick: handle hardware_ril/ril-caf
  *jrior001 - repopick: skip abandoned commits
  *Marcos Marado - Adding msm8909 as a QCOM board platform
  *Scott Mertz - build: Kernel: arm64 uses Image.gz as the target
  *Tao Bao - Change the cache partition size check into warnings.
  *Tao Bao - Revise stash for BBOTAs when needed.
  *Tao Bao - Free the stash after its use in BBOTA v2.
  *Tao Bao - Assert the stash size when generating OTAs.
  *Sami Tolvanen - Check partition hash before resorting to block_image_verify
  *Sami Tolvanen - Calculate max_stashed_blocks correctly for block OTA v3
  *Tao Bao - Restrict the verification in block-based incremental OTAs
  *Michael Runge - Do not use block_verify on target-files where feature is missing.
  *Jesse Zhao - Fix the error that free_string is not defined.
  *Ricardo Cerqueira - product: Let a device customize its own locales
  *Sami Tolvanen - Change transfer list format to include block hashes
  *Tom Powell - Support custom gerrit servers via HTTP or SSH
  *Rashed Abdel-Tawab - build: Enable A53 errata workarounds on targets that need it
  *Andreas Blaesius - Force bsdiff for recovery_from_boot.p if not using GZIP
  *Bernhard Rosenkränzer - Don't use -Wl,--fix-cortex-a8 for Cortex A7, A9, A15, Krait or Denver
  *Bernhard Rosenkränzer - Allow -mcpu=cortex-a15 for clang
  *Ian Rogers - Move definition of -D__ARM_FEATURE_LPAE=1 cflag to top-level.
  *arter97 - Apply correct, optimized mfpu compiler flag for ARMv7-A Cortex CPUs
  *Matt Mower - build: Enable custom ccache cache dir for Android
  *Adnan Begovic - build/core: Allow EXTERNAL_CLEAN_TARGETS to dump vars.
  *Brint E. Kriebel - roomservice: use force-sync when adding projects with roomservice
  *Brint E. Kriebel - build: Fix extra userdata generation some more
  *Brint E. Kriebel - build: Fix extra userdata generation
  *Andrew Sutherland - build: add cmremote function
  *Andrew Sutherland - build: add crremote function
  *Rabih Salamey - build: cut out crrebase, crremote and crgerrit functions
  *Brint E. Kriebel - otatools: Only build f2fs tools on Linux
  *Brint E. Kriebel - otatools: Add f2fs tools to otatools builds
  *Brint E. Kriebel - build: Allow packaging of factory image files into target files
  *Brint E. Kriebel - misc_info: Add factory script location to misc_info when available
  *Chirayu Desai - Allow setting the recovery density separately from the aapt config
  *David Ng - arm64: Enable Cortex A53 Errata 843419, 835769 ldflags
  *Wei Wang - AArch64: Addressing Cortex-A53 erratum 835769
  *Steve Kondik - Revert "Disable -mcpu=cortex-a15 flag for krait"
  *Ameya Thakur - tools:releasetools:Use timestamp from build.prop while building system.img
  *Steve Kondik - build: Fix device detection for a few of the envsetup commands
  *Steve Kondik - build: Fix image creation for F2FS-only configuration
  *Steve Kondik - releasetools: Add support for LZMA in blockimgdiff
  *Myself5 - Revert "Build: Add Custom Toolchain Support"
  *Myself5 - Revert "Introduce Custom Compiler Flags"
  *Edward Wang - Revert "build: use common factory script and input more parameters"
  *The Android Automerger - "LMY48G"
  *The Android Automerger - "LMY48F"
  *The Android Automerger - "LMY48E"
  *The Android Automerger - "LMY48D"
  *The Android Automerger - "LMY48C"
  *Andrew Boie - definitions.mk: look for definitions.mk in device/*/build also
  *Ying Wang - Really include drawables for all densities.
  *Edward Wang - build: use common factory script and input more parameters
  *Howard M. Harte - minnow_max: search for cm.mk in additional directories
  *Matt Mower - envsetup: repolastsync
  *Chirayu Desai - otasigcheck: Extract the key
  *Chirayu Desai - otasigcheck: Extract the key
  *Diogo Ferreira - build: Add the factorypackage target
  *Adnan Begovic - build/core: Inherit vendor/* makefiles for check-api.
  *Chris Sarbora - Allow dopush to load binaries onto the "wrong" device
  *STELIX - Revert "Build - RoomService: Set "default_team_rem" to "gh" for now"
  *Myself5 - repopick: link to carbon gerrit
  *Myself5 - update envsetup with our KK code for crremote
  *Myself5 - Introduce Custom Compiler Flags
  *Anthony King - envsetup: cleanup the full list
  *Anthony King - lunch: sort the choices
  *Hashcode - build: avoid recovery patch if device setup can't do it correctly
  *Anthony King - envsetup: add mk_timer

Project name: android_system_core
  *Diogo Ferreira - fs_mgr: When formating ext4 volumes, respect the length parameter
  *Sultan Qasim Khan - fs_mgr: zram: allow specifying stream count
  *Keith Mok - Fix build break for multiple definition
  *Steve Kondik - init: Fire a trigger when a class is started/stopped
  *Krzysztof Adamski - sdcard: Properly handle deleted nodes
  *Johan Redestig - sdcard: Turn on noatime for fuse mounted sdcard
  *Jaegeuk Kim - Revert "fs_mgr: let fsck.f2fs actually attempt a fix"
  *Thomas Wendt - libcutils/liblog: Add functions required by Huawei g620_a2 binaries
  *Adam Lesinski - Prevent integer overflow when allocating native_handle_t
  *Chris Fries - init: Add support for gzipped firmware files
  *Mrcl1450 - healthd: Add secondary backlight path support
  *Steve Kondik - init: Add a "starting" state for services
  *Chao Chen - healthd: Support QC2.0 type charger
  *Tony Layher - Added umount to init
  *Steve Kondik - libutils: Improve support for POSIX timers
  *Jorge Ruesga - healthd: dock battery
  *Chao Chen - Charger: Add font to show real battery capacity in charger mode.
  *Ethan Chen - Add Wileyfox VID part 2
  *Ethan Chen - Add Wileyfox VID
  *Scott Mertz - healthd: allow custom charger
  *Jesse Hall - Mutex: add timedLock() method
  *Pete Delaney - Provide better advice on using gdb with debuggerd on crashed applications.
  *Arne Coucheron - audio: fix incall music ifdefs (1/3)
  *cpasjuste - liblog: add Amazon logging functions for prebuilt compatibility

Project name: android_system_extras_su
  *Pawit Pornkitprasan - su: allow init to automatically restart daemon

Project name: android_system_extras
  *Edward Wang - f2fs_utils: fix block alignment calculation
  *Keith Mok - Add darwin support for the host tools
  *Mihai Serban - make_ext4fs: workaround for a glibc scandir bug
  *Andrew Boie - fix keystore_signer
  *Tom Marshall - make_ext4fs: Fix mac build
  *Tom Marshall - make_ext4fs: Support kernel transparent compression v2

</Changelog>
</ROM>
